你那位所谓的魔术师在哪
Where in hell is your so-called magician?
他会来的  兰斯洛特
He will be here, Lancelot.
他发过誓
He swore it.
他们准备发起第二轮进攻了
They're preparing for a second wave.
冲锋
Charge!
这  这看起来就像世界末日一样
This... This is what the end looks like.
你所谓的魔术师梅林帮不了我们
Your so-called magician, Merlin, cannot help us.
我们寡不敌众  要以一敌百
We're outnumbered, 100 to 1.
怎么才能杀出重围
How are we gonna get out of this?
他答应给我一件强大的武器
He promised a weapon, one of great power.
亚瑟  你是我的王
Arthur, you are my king.
我愿为你献出我的生命
I will lay down my life for you,
但这个梅林不是巫师
but this Merlin is no wizard.
他就是个不值一提的醉鬼
He's a worthless drunkard!
天哪  我真的醉了
God, I'm sozzled!
最后一口
One last nip.
魔法确实存在
Magic does exist.
在很久以前  它被发现于
It was found, long ago,
一艘坠落的外星飞船里
inside a crashed alien ship.
有人吗
Hello?
哈罗
Hello!
是我
It is I,
那个招魂者  黑魔法大师
conjurer of spirits, master of the dark arts!
有人在吗
Is anyone there?
是我  梅林
It is I, Merlin.
那个巫师
The wizard?
记得我吗
Remember me?
不  我帮你保密了  真的  我没有食言
No! I kept your secret! I did! Just as I promised!
我没和任何人提起你的存在  任何人
I told no one of your existence. No one!
但你得理解  我们不列颠人
But you have to understand, we Britons
正在进行一场生死大战
are in a desperate fight.
真的是走投无路了  我是认真的
End-of-times sort of thing. I mean it.
就在我们说话的这会儿  我的族人在浴血奋战
It's happening down there now as we speak.
相当糟糕
It's awful!
刀光剑影的  杀的非常激烈
Big personalities just sort of clashing and bloody.
我实在难以启齿  但我们需要你的帮助
I hate to ask... But we need your help.
没有咒语  也没有魔法
There are no spells. There is no magic.
我们撤退  择日再战
We retreat. Live to fight another day.
不行
No!
没有牺牲  哪来的胜利
Without sacrifice... There can be no victory.
你真是疯了
This is madness!
他会来的
He will be here.
好吧  我就和他们说的那样
All right, I am what they say!
我是个骗子  是个冒牌货  我这辈子都在坑蒙拐骗
I'm a liar, I'm a charlatan. I've deceived my whole life.
但如果我可以  哪怕只有一刻
But if I could, for one moment,
改变世界  让它变得更好
change this world for the better,
我会放弃其他一切  一切
I would give up everything. Everything!
我会戒酒  戒钱  戒女人
I'd give up drink, money, wom...
就戒酒和戒钱
Drink and money.
听着
Look.
没有你的帮忙  很多好人都会死
Good men will die without your help.
还有女人和孩子
Women. Children.
我知道你的世界毁灭了  抱歉
I know your world was destroyed. I'm sorry.
但请别让我们也重蹈覆辙
But please don't let ours die, too.
算我求你了
I beg of you.
守护骑士  变形  巨龙听候你的差遣
Guardian Knights, transform. Dragon is yours to command.
太好了
Yes.
那正是我想要的
That would be just the thing.
保护好这个权杖
Protect this staff.
日后会有邪恶势力来夺取它
One day a great evil will come for it.
太棒了
Yes!
冲锋
Charge!
有句代代相传的话说道
It has been said through the ages,
没有牺牲
without sacrifice,
哪来的胜利
there can be no victory.
宇宙中有很多谜团
There are mysteries to the universe
我们我们无法解开解开
we were never meant to solve.
我是擎天柱
I am Optimus Prime
有句话要传给我的创造者
and this message is to my creators:
离地球远点
Leave planet Earth alone.
因为我来了
'Cause I'm coming
冲你们来了
for you.
变形金刚  最后的骑士
TRANSFORMERS: THE LAST KNIGHT
适逢多事之秋
These are troubled times.
擎天柱离开我们去寻找他的创造者
Optimus Prime has left us to find his makers.
有些人说他不会再回来了
Some say he will never return.
而他的死敌威震天  也销声匿迹了
His sworn enemy, Megatron... Vanished.
群龙无首  混沌当道
Without leaders, chaos reigns.
两大阵营开战
Two species at war.
血肉之躯对垒钢筋铁骨
One flesh, one metal.
变形金刚在地球上被列为非法的存在
Transformers are declared illegal on Earth.
世界上成立了一种新的准军事部队
The world has set up a new paramilitary force.
变形金刚反应部队
The TRF.
除了古巴
Except in Cuba,
卡斯特罗允许汽车人在沙滩上晒太阳
Castro lets them sun on his beaches.
朋友  来嘛  出来玩吧
Hola, amigo! Come on! Vamonos!
- 不行  他很忙  - 他老是很忙
- No, he's busy. -He's always busy.
莫吉托（鸡尾酒）需要冰
A mojito needs ice.
冰
Ice!
我们不是动物
We are not animals.
但这些外星人还在不断从天而降
But these alien beings keep arriving.
一波接着一波
Endless waves of them.
无以计数
Too many to count.
我们带着恐慌望向天空  不禁疑惑
We look to the skies with dread and we wonder.
就是这首  我喜欢这首歌
This is the jam! I like this.
选得好  选得好
Good choice. Good choice.
把脚从我桌上拿开
Get it off my desk.
不会吧
No way!
从哪弄来的
Where'd you get that?
我们还剩多少时间
How much of our time remains?
在宇宙中亿万的行星中
One hundred billion trillion planets in the cosmos...
快打电话给局长  快  快  快
No, get the Director on the phone. Go, go, go!
他们选择了地球
And they choose Earth.
为什么
Why?
你们想见识下机器人尸体吗
Y'all want to see some dead robots?
你疯了吗  这是外星人禁区
You crazy? This is an alien No-Go Zone.
政府不想让我们进去
Government doesn't want us to go in here.
我们不该来这的
We're not supposed to be here.
伙计  我们是小孩  他们不会拿我们怎样
We're kids, man. We get away with anything.
我看未必
Nah, man.
我要拿走个纪念品
I'm getting me a souvenir.
这可都是真家伙
This is the real deal.
那边有个死的
There's a dead one over there.
- 酷  - 一点都不酷
- Cool! - Not cool.
是变形金刚反应部队干的
TRF shot 'em down.
管他呢  我把说先把他们干趴下  让老天爷决定他们的生死
Whatever. My dad says shoot 'em all and let God sort them out.
吉娃娃
Chihuahua.
- 兄弟  那是什么  - 老兄
- Bro, what is that? - Dude.
这是个机器人
It's a robot!
老兄  我觉得它死了
Dude, I think it's dead.
怎么会  老兄
Nah, bro.
是的  它死透了
Yeah, it's totally dead.
他绝对  绝对死了
He's definitely, definitely dead.
我知道  好吗
I know, right?
等等伙计们  我觉得它在动
Wait, guys. I think it's moving.
警告  非法闯入
Warning! Unauthorized trespassing.
- 该死  - 我们是美国国土安全局
- Shit. - This is the Department of Homeland Security.
你们闯入了一个外星人污染的区域
You are trespassing in an alien contamination zone.
请平静地走出来  并投降
Please step forward calmly and surrender.
看这里  混蛋
Mira, puto!
叽叽  动手
Sqweeks! Do it!
跟我来
Follow me!
快  起来
Come on, get up!
长官  这片区域有情况
Hey, sir. This area is active.
我们两个哨兵被放倒了
We just had two Sentinels go down.
怎么回事
What have you got?
千万别回头看
Never look back!
- 它来了  - 好了  快进去
- It's coming! - All right, go in there.
该死  我都快得心脏病了
Damn. I almost had a heart attack!
放松  我们有掩体
Relax. We're covered.
叽叽
Sqweeks!
那是什么
What's that?
你怎么
What the...
你的胳膊怎么了
What happened to your arm?
你被打中了
Shot you?
该死
Damn it!
他不能变形了
He can't transform.
我试着修好他
I'm trying to fix him.
但你有点娇气了  叽叽
But you're being a baby about it, Sqweeks.
没事  你做的很好
It's all right. You did good.
你心可真大
You have a big heart...
看起来起作用了
That seems to be working.
你多久健一次身
What's your workout routine?
没事  没事  我都说了
It's all right. It's all right. I told you.
这个掩体  他叫天幕
"Covered." It's Canopy.
独眼巨人  把镜头移到目标上
Cyclops, zoom in on target.
没法确认身份  看到有5个小家伙
Unable PID. Visual on five little feathers.
小孩  坏了
Kids. Shit.
无法确认是狂派
Cannot confirm Decepticon.
没有徽章  这些孩子危险了
No badge. I got kids in danger.
- 养天幕可真是太疯狂了  - 这不关你的事
- Canopy thing's pretty crazy. - It's none of your business.
别打情骂俏了
Stop flirting.
请求空中支援  保持距离  不要开火
Request immediate air support. Danger close. Do not fire.
- 他是谁  - 我们走
- Who is he? -Let's go.
对你来说  他是我男朋友
Far as you're concerned, my boyfriend.
你俩在一起多久了
How long's that been going on?
你们这些小孩得离开这
You kids gotta get out of here.
孩子  你不也是
"Kids"? You're here.
我住在这
I live here.
这是我家
This is my home.
这是哪儿  客厅还是餐厅
What's this? The living room or the dining room?
总得有人照顾他们啊
Someone's gotta take care of 'em.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
- 他们受了惊吓  迷失了  - 快点
- They're scared. They're lost. - Hurry.
我发现一处热感应  显示有威胁
I've got a heat signature. Hostile intent is displayed.
对方有武器
Tango is armed.
30秒就位  我要开火吗
On location 30 seconds. Am I cleared to fire?
没有家  没有家人  没有容身之地  你能体会吗
No, place, no home, no family. Do you know how that feels?
不能  因为你们能回家住大房子去
No, 'cause your asses got big old houses to go home to.
我家是公寓楼
We got a condo.
我喜欢她
I love her.
毒蛇战斗机  我们需要许可
Viper Flight. We need a clearance.
没有徽章  有武器且有敌意  孩子们会有危险
No badge, armed and hostile. I got kids in danger.
威胁  威胁
Hostile intent. Hostile intent.
- 外星人装备了武器  - 开火
- Alien has a weapon. - Fire!
他被打趴下了  B队  救出那些孩子
He's down. Bravo team, extract those kids.
我们出发
We're moving out!
- 起来  - 我不行了
- Get up. - I can't.
不  不  不  看着我
No, no, no, look at me.
醒醒  天幕  你会好起来的
Wake up, Canopy! You're gonna be okay.
我想谢谢你
I want to thank you.
醒醒  看着我  醒醒  天幕  我不会离开你
Wake up, look at me. Wake up, Canopy. I'm not leaving you.
你是我仅剩的一切
You're all I have left!
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我马上就要放大招了  你们最好上车
Hey! It's all I got in my bag of tricks, so you might want to hop in.
车钥匙在哪
Hey! Where are the keys?
Where are the keys?
我直接短路搞定它
I'm just gonna hotwire this bitch.
天天找我麻烦  我都烦了
I'm tired of people messing with me.
结束了
It's over.
不  我能修好他
No! I can fix him.
没人能修好他  他死了
Nobody can fix him, he's dead.
看着我  他希望看到你死吗
Hey, look at me. Would he want you to die, too?
快走吧  快
Let's go, now.
快跑  快跑
Come on, come on!
快点  快点  没时间了  走
Come on. Come on, no time, let's go.
等等  你就是那人
What? Hey, you're that guy.
不  我不是那人
No, I'm not that guy.
那个救变形金刚的人
The one who saves Transformers.
我本认为你就是个传说
I thought you were just a legend.
传说又怎样
Some legend.
- 你来得太迟了  - 走  走
- You were too late! - Go. Go.
你知道举报你有奖吗
Hey, you know there's a reward for turning you in.
- 真的  - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
好啊  你想小脸被揍开花吗
Cool. You want to get punched in the face, like, really hard?
不想
No.
- 很好  进去  - 好的
- Good. Go. - Okay.
你就是个白痴
You're such an idiot.
回见  传奇
See ya around, "legend."
叽叽
Sqweeks.
放松  放松  好吗
Easy. Easy, all right?
我来这帮你的
I'm just here to help you.
别急  伙计
Easy, buddy. Yeah.
你伤的真重
You're hurt really bad. All right?
保护好它  别被昆
Protect from Quin...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
拿着
Take the...
这个护身符会保护你
The talisman will protect you.
你不欠我任何东西
You don't owe me anything.
古塞伯坦语
Seglass ni Tonday.
我不能拿  你留着吧
I can't. You keep it.
昆  昆
Quin... Quin...
他没挺过来  大黄蜂  我一个人出来了
He didn't make it, Bee. I'm coming out solo.
今天看来要变得更糟了
This is turning into one shitty-ass day.
独眼巨人  盯紧大鱼
Cyclops, eyeball Kingfish.
把红外线调成光电传感器
Flip IR to EO.
长官  他相当吻合  是凯德·耶格
He's a positive match, sir. It's Cade Yeager.
结束了  帮你自己一把吧
It's over. Help yourself out here.
其他人在哪  被你藏起来的在哪
Where are the others? The ones you're hiding.
我不会出卖朋友的
I don't sell out friends.
朋友
"Friends."
这是一场侵略
This is an invasion.
当有天我们醒来时  地球就变他们的了
One day we wake up... They're in charge.
你看见有谁想统治地球了
You see anybody in charge?
他们只是不停得从天上掉下来
They just keep falling out of the sky.
天上掉东西   你没办法用枪解决
Something's coming, and you can't shoot your way out of it.
那是什么
What was that?
那是个错误
That was a mistake.
当心  当心  当心
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
下次你再开枪打谁
Next time you shoot somebody,
先确定他死了再靠近他
don't go near 'em till you're sure they're dead.
把武器放下  相信我
Put the weapon down, trust me!
放松  大黄蜂  放松
Easy, Bee. Easy.
我会把你烧得让你希望自己没出生
I'll burn you so bad you'll wish you'd died as a child.
打他啊
Shoot him!
你肯定死在我前面
You're dead before I hit the ground.
- 我说了停火  - 开抢  快
- I said stand down. -Shoot! Shoot!
开枪
Take the shot!
Shoot!
住手  黄蜂
Don't do it, Bee!
别开火  停下
Hold your fire! Hold it!
你  放下枪
You! Drop it!
想得美
I'm not dropping shit.
军方也不像这样  黄蜂  你要相信我们
The military doesn't want it this way, Bee, you gotta believe that.
现在政权变了  这些人说了算
It's a new world order now and these guys are calling the shots.
他们只想要一个家  你心里明白得很
All they want is a home, and you know it.
要是逼他们  他们会立马反击
You push them, and they push right back.
猎犬来了
Hound's in town.
最喜欢早晨打一战了
Love starting the day off with a gunfight.
抱歉我来晚了  我来这劲爆舞会的邀请信
Sorry I'm late. My invitation to this ass-kicking
肯定是寄丢了
must've got lost in the mail!
我和队员要撤了
Me and my crew are rolling out of here.
- 把你的飞机撤走  - 我们走
- Call off your birds. -Let's go.
他们不会动我们的
They're not gonna touch us.
星空一号  撤离  没发现霸天虎的踪迹
All right, Star 1, abort. Negative Decepticon activity.
变形金刚反应部队别动  放下枪
TRF, stand fast. Drop your guns.
你确定不开枪吗  我可是你们的目标呢
You sure you don't want to shoot? I'm a big ol' target.
胆小鬼
Wusses.
你到底站哪一边
Whose side are you on?
他们都是坏人
They're all bad.
才不是
No, they're not.
鹰眼  标记他
Eagle Eye, tag him.
我从未见过像它这样的  将军
I've never seen one like it, General.
这个更古老  比擎天柱还老
This one's older, older than Optimus Prime.
路障也在同样的地点被发现
Decepticon Barricade was spotted at that same location.
CIA在他身上用了捕食者监视他有一阵了
CIA's had him under Pred surveillance for a while now.
他一直和一些有趣的对象有来往
Yeah, he's been keeping some interesting company.
权杖被藏在地球上
The staff is hidden on Earth.
充满终极力量的武器
A weapon of ultimate power.
我们会找到它
We'll find this staff.
那声音
That voice.
就像噩梦里一样
I can hear it in my nightmares.
- 威震天  - 有待确认
-Megatron. - Waiting for authentication.
就是他
It's him.
威震天大人
Lord Megatron.
别照着我的脸
Get that out of my face.
汇报
Report.
请告诉我你找到了护身符
Tell me you have found the talisman.
我看到了  一个濒死骑士交给了人类
I saw it. A dying knight gave it to a human.
但那里有太多变形金刚反应部队人力了
But there was too much TRF firepower.
你居然让护身符被别人夺走了
You let the talisman get away!
我们必须得到它
We must have it!
没有护身符  我们就无法找到权杖
Without the talisman, we cannot find the staff!
我知道谁能带我们找到
I know who can lead us to it.
变形金刚反应部队
The TRF.
总司令命令那武器
Commander in Chief wants that weapon,
或者叫它权杖  不论一切都要保护好
or "staff" as he calls it, secured at all cost.
保留你在变形金刚反应部队的卧底身份
Maintain your covert embed with TRF.
长官  他们只是不懂
Sir... They just don't get it.
我们与大黄蜂还有变形金刚的历史
Our history with Bee and the Autobots.
我们多希望擎天柱能回来
What we would all give to have Prime back right now.
擎天柱
Optimus Prime.
再次进入赛伯坦
Re-entry Cybertron.
我的世界
My world!
我的世界怎么了
What has happened to my world?
你的世界濒临死亡
Your world is dying.
我在等你  擎天柱
I've been waiting for you, Optimus.
来见见你的创造者
Come meet your maker.
你是我的创造者
You are my creator?
我是昆塔沙  造物主
I am Quintessa, the Prime of Life.
你对我的家圆做了什么
What have you done to my home?
我要杀了你
I will kill you!
你胆敢袭击你的神
You dare to strike your god?
你的战争毁了赛博坦
Your war doomed Cybertron.
是威震天挑起的战争
Megatron started the war!
是你摧毁了你的世界  蠢货
You destroyed your world, you fool.
我完美的造物
My perfect creation.
你去修正这一切
You're going to fix it,
否则变形金刚会永远绝迹
or the race of Transformers dies forever.
我创造了你
I made you.
所以要听我的命令
You are mine to command.
怎么跑到这来的
How did you get in here?
主人  我们等了1600年
My lord, that weird thing
才发生的奇怪现象出现了
we've been waiting for 1,600 years to happen...
我想这次是真的了
I think it's really happening this time!
骑士们到了
The knight has arrived.
护身符被赠与了正确之人
The talisman has been bestowed.
终于  考格曼  开始了
At last, Cogman. It begins.
我的
Mine!
太好了
Yes!
谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
温布利  我有空
Wembly! I was quite open.
你经常空闲是有原因的
There's a reason why you're always open.
你一直单身也是有理由的
There's a reason you're always single.
- 什么  - 什么
- What? - What?
蠢货
Idiot.
天啊  好吧
God. Okay.
迟到了  迟到了
So late, so late, so late.
公元 484   在人类文明与野蛮之间最后一搏
484 CE. A desperate last stand between civilization and barbarism.
两个世界发生碰撞
Two worlds colliding.
只有一个世界能够幸存
Only one survives.
兰斯洛特  珀西瓦尔
Lancelot. Percival.
亚瑟王
King Arthur.
都是值得尊敬的人
Honorable men.
英勇无畏  体格强健
Brave, muscles sinewed,
甲光向日金鳞开
sweat glistening off their bodies.
他们是仅有几位愿意为胜利献出一切的人
A few brave men who were willing to sacrifice all for victory.
听着太不真实了吧  波比
Sound too good to be true, Poppy?
因为都是扯淡
Because it's horseshit.
亚瑟王
Arthur.
可能是罗马将军与凯尔特人国王的结合体
A likely composite of a Roman general and a Celtic king.
我们的龙
Our dragon.
只是只中世纪的投石机
Just a medieval catapult.
然后梅林
And then we have Merlin,
拥立国王者
our Kingmaker.
可能从未存在过
Probably never existed.
问题是
The question is,
为什么  为什么我们要给自己编这些故事
why? Why do we tell ourselves these stories?
除了广而告之龙是邪恶之外
Other than the fact that dragons are wicked.
因为那是我们希望相信
It's because we want to believe.
希望这些英雄存在于我们的生活中
Believe that we can be heroes in our own lives.
当世界崩塌
When all seems lost,
仅剩下我们几位勇敢的人
a few brave souls, us,
能够拯救我们所知的一切
can save everything we've ever known.
还是说只有龙
Or is it just the dragons?
好吧
Well,
不用很久了  老朋友
it won't be much longer now, old friend.
世界末日的迹象就在我们身边
Signs of the end are all around us.
你知道怎么做  是不是
You know what to do, don't you?
我们必须重建家园
We must rebuild my home.
有办法拯救你的世界
There is a way to heal your world.
我的创造力的源泉  权杖
My power of creation, the staff,
被我的12位守护骑士偷走
was stolen from me by my 12 guardian knights.
他们背叛了我将它藏在了地球上
They betrayed me and hid it on Earth.
把它给了你珍视的人类
Gave it to your precious humans.
权杖是唯一能让赛博坦重获生机
The staff is the only way to bring life back to Cybertron.
你帮我去找到它
You are going to find it for me.
你想要得到救赎吗  擎天柱
Do you seek redemption, Prime?
想吗
Do you?
我的造物主
My maker,
我想
I do.
不要害怕  不要憎恨  也不要愤怒
No fear. No hate. No anger.
别碰我  你这个蛆虫
Get off, you maggot!
我要杀了你  飞鼠
I will kill you, flying rat!
他还很小  很烦人
He's very little. Very tiring.
坐在这丧失理智
Losing our heads sitting around here.
受够了隐藏
So tired of hiding.
酋长  真是
Hey, Chief! Nice...
天
God!
真是匹好马
Nice horse you got there.
你还真是对这些印第安东西着了迷
You're really getting into this whole Indian thing?
别叫我酋长  我叫雪曼
Don't call me Chief. My name is Sherman.
你不是酋长吗
Aren't you the tribal chief?
嗯  但听起来似乎
Yeah. But from you it sounds...
不知道  有点种族歧视啊
I don't know, vaguely racist.
- 我的巡逻车被偷了  - 什么
- My cruiser got stolen. -What?
- 第二次了  - 太惨了
- Again. - That's terrible!
你猜怎么的
You know what?
事态控制不住了
Shit's getting out of control.
到处都是犯罪
There's crime going on everywhere!
我很多东西都被偷了
A bunch of my stuff got stolen.
别扯淡  凯德  把我车还我
Cut the shit, Cade... And get me my car back.
大成功
Booyah! Big time.
一直就想说了
Been holding that one in for a while.
该死  忘了还有个集束炸弹了
Damn, forgot about that cluster bomb.
喂
Yo!
有什么毛病  老兄
What's your problem, dude?
下回  刹车轻一点
Next time, ease on the brakes!
这是我的风格  我喜欢隆重出场
That's the way I roll. I like to make a statement when I arrive.
营地都被你弄上灰了
Well, you're getting dust all over the campus!
这里才不是营地  是垃圾场
This ain't no campus. It's a junkyard!
快点  快点   快来  快来
Come on, hustle. ?ándale! ?ándale!
吉米
Jimmy!
别冲我发火
Hey, don't take any aggression out on me.
该死  钢锁  我们是客人
Damn it, Grimlock! We're guests here!
你陷入麻烦了吗
You got in some shit?
都快找上门了
Yeah, neck deep!
凯德  这就是你带大黄蜂出去的下场
Cade, that's what you get for taking the yellow bugger.
你需要找个领导  比如我
You need a leader out there... Like me.
闭嘴  免得我给你带来
Shut up. Before I do some damage
无法恢复的伤害
you won't walk away from.
你永远成不了擎天柱
You will never be Optimus Prime.
话太多
You talk too much.
拜托  老兄  百万多岁的传奇战士
Come on, man. Million-year-old legendary warrior
你们却表现的像一堆垃圾狗一样
and you act like a bunch of junkyard dogs!
你惹毛我了
You're starting to piss me off!
吉娃娃
Ay, chihuahua!
快回来  钢锁
Come back here, Grimlock!
转过来  你嘴里有什么
Turn around. What do you got in your mouth?
我发誓  保护你是浪费时间
I swear, I am wasting my time protecting you.
放下巡逻车
Drop the cruiser right now!
我知道你吃了雪曼司令的巡逻车
I know you got Chief Sherman's cruiser.
放下
Drop it!
这样才对  吐出来  快
Serves you right. Spit it out! Spit it!
别吃车  别吃车
Don't eat cars. Don't eat cars.
回到你的洞去  反省反省
You get back in your hole and think about what you did.
就好像是梅西百货感恩节的游行一样热闹啊  吉米
It's like the Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade out here, Jimmy J.
你从达科塔分账报的一则招人启示中雇佣了我
You hired me from a want ad in the Dakota Penny Ledger.
你以为我有超能力吗
Think that comes with a superpower?
那是恐龙  外星恐龙
That is a dinosaur! An alien dinosaur!
广告里可没说
That was not in the ad!
昨天还想吃了我来着
It tried to eat me yesterday.
你想进联邦监狱吗
You want to go to federal prison?
不  我不想进任何监狱
No, no, I don't want to go to any prison.
你肯定要进监狱的
Well, that's where you're gonna go, okay?
因为你是从犯
'Cause you're aiding and abetting.
我是逃犯
I'm a fugitive, all right?
我是大老板  你只是我的小喽啰
I'm the big boss, you're my little crimey.
你走后
When you leave,
这就变得跟动物世界一样
it becomes the Wild Kingdom out here.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do.
我说过这里是垃圾场
I told you, this is a junkyard.
他们和垃圾融为一体了  仅此而已
They blend in with other junk. That's it.
你将我雇佣为国际公司的高级副主席
You hired me to be senior vice president of worldwide operations.
- 我说过吗  - 你是这么说的
- Did I tell you that? - Yes, that's what you said.
我瞎编的
I made that shit up.
请别把我的头衔拿走  凯德
Do not take this title away from me, Cade.
这里不是创业公司  我干这个不是为了赚钱
This is not a startup, okay? I don't do this shit for money.
是为了更远大的事业
It's for the higher cause.
你不是为了赚钱吗
You don't do this shit for the money?
你有什么毛病  你打算怎么吃
What's wrong with you? How you gonna eat?
他来这做什么
What's he doing here?
地球上最烦人的变形金刚来了
Here comes the most irritating, annoying Transformer on Earth.
我应该袭击他吗
Should I frag him?
他为了过那个门给了你什么
What did he give you to get past the gate?
什么都没给
Nothing!
凯德  他把这个给了他
Hey, Cade. He gave him this.
我从来没见过这个
I've never seen that before in my life.
说出来  你想要那外星炸弹
Come on, say it! You wanted the alien blaster.
你说过真男人要有好枪
You said a big gun makes a big man.
你知道人类脾气不好  对吧
Hey, you know human beings lose their temper, right?
- 你敢  - 过来
- Don't you dare! Hey, hey! - Come here!
最糟糕的高级副主席
The worst senior vice president...
停下  停下
Stop it! Stop it!
你真男人  你健身了吗
Yeah, you're real tough! What, you been working out?
- 我要去炸他  - 绝对的
- I'm going to frag him. - Definitely frag him.
我听到了  探长
I heard that, Hound.
别冲动
Easy!
天  你总是靠暴力解决问题
God. You always resort to violence right off the bat.
我喜欢暴力
I love violence.
交易员  你怎么会在这
Daytrader! The hell are you doing here?
找到你的太空船了吗
You find our spaceship yet?
我不想在这附近晃悠了
I'm getting tired of hanging around here,
简直是等死
waiting to catch a bullet.
一氧化碳  以及或许偶尔的酗汽油
Carbon monoxide, and perhaps a small gasoline drinking problem
在子弹打死你之前就能让你死  我的胖友
are gonna kill you long before a bullet, my corpulent comrade.
- 滚  别让我看到你  - 小心  伙计们  停下
- Back off! Get out of my face. - Watch it! Guys, stop!
你想和探长打一架吗
You want to throw down with Hound?
硬汉  没礼貌
Tough guy? Rude.
你来拿这些东西怎么样
How about you trying to carry all this stuff?
看我在布法罗找到了什么
Look what I found in Buffalo.
红蜘蛛的头  女士们先生们
Starscream's head, ladies and gentlemen.
看我找到了什么  大黄蜂有新音箱了
Look what I got. New voice box for Bee.
这回会成功吗
Is it gonna work this time?
我只有好东西  凯德  好不好
I only got the good stuff, Cade. Come on.
听到了吗  黄蜂  你能说话了  兄弟
You hear that, Bee? You're gonna talk, buddy!
蹲下  黄蜂
Get down, Bee!
你还有什么
All right, what else you got?
你从哪拿的那垃圾
Where'd you get that piece of junk?
这垃圾堆里会有守护骑士的护身符
A Knight of lacon talisman in this dump?
绝对不是真的
Nah, it's not real.
是吗  不  绝不是真的
Is it? No, definitely not.
嘿  给我  我帮你处理掉
Hey, give it to me, I'll take it off you.
你以为我不知道这玩意是什么吗  有多重要
You think I don't know what the hell this is? How valuable?
但我知道这肯定很重要  因为
But I know it's something, because it's got you
你对这玩意垂涎欲滴  你个邋遢鬼
licking your chops, you skank.
说话真伤人  凯德
Words hurt, Cade.
一共有七个  数一数
There are exactly seven... Count them.
七个天气来临的征兆
Seven signs of the apocalypse.
那里的那个护身符出现就是第一个
And that talisman showing up here is numero uno.
如果那个可爱的铁饼是真的
If that fancy pancake was real,
我会抓起宇宙飞船  然后让这个脏兮兮的星球灰飞烟灭
I'd grab the spaceship and blow this dirtball planet.
好吧  我得给自己涂点油了
All right, I'm gonna go slather myself in oil.
如果你感觉不适的话  漂移  转过去
Turn your back, Drift, if it offends your sensibilities.
那种东西可是很难视而不见的
Now that is something you can't unsee.
我不太理解你在说什么
I barely understand what's coming out of your mouth.
嘿  嘿  先生
Hey! Hey, mister!
这可不行
This isn't happening.
你不能呆在这里  孩子  我这已经不少流浪汉了
You cannot stay here, kid. I got enough strays.
我不是小孩  我很有用的  我会修东西
I'm not a kid! I'm useful. I fix shit.
- 那太棒了  - 比别人都厉害
- Yeah, good for you. - Better than anyone.
而且我有名字
And I have a name, you know.
是伊莎贝拉  有字母z的那个
It's Izabella. Izabella with a Z.
我才不关心带不带z或者颜文字  还是美元符号神马的
I don't care if it's a Z, an emoji, or a dollar sign,
好吗  我这里可没地方给
all right? This is no place for...
回家吧  拜托了
Just go home. Please.
我没有家
I don't got a home.
而且他们
And they...
而且他们刚刚杀了
They just killed
我最后一位可称为家人的生灵
the last thing that I called family.
所以  不
So no,
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
我想留下  并且和他们对抗
I want to stay and I want to fight them.
你没法与他们对抗  你也不可能打败他们
You can't fight them, and you can't beat them.
好吗  整个世界都支持他们
All right? They have the support of the entire world.
而你  你只是个孩子
You, you're a kid.
你怎么还跟着我
Why are you still following me?
T
T!
第一次喷火  哥们
First flames, dude!
嘿  先生  你的拖车着火了
Hey! Mister! Your trailer's on fire.
嘿  到转角那
Hey, corner.
我的天啊  哥们  我为你自豪
My God. Buddy! I'm proud of you.
但是你得去外面喷火  好吗
I know, but you gotta do it outside now, okay?
不然你会把这里都烧没了的
You could burn this whole place down.
我知道  但是你现在能量过剩  好吗
I know, but you're coming into your power now, all right?
所以你要喷火  不
So you gotta blow the flames... No.
特里  帮我拿个啤酒好吗
Terry, get me a beer, will ya?
嘿  伙计们  你们得停下
Hey, guys, you gotta cut the crap.
你们把所有东西都弄坏了
You're tearing everything apart.
送的好  哥们  只是拿的水平还得提高
Perfect delivery, buddy. You gotta work on the pickup.
我还得训练他
I still got him in training.
你家人怎么了
What happened to your family?
你先说
You first.
妻子过世了  女儿在上大学
Wife passed away. Daughter's at college.
她也有可能登月了
She might as well be on the moon.
至少她还在  兄弟
At least she's still here, bro.
要是我去看她  我们都得被抓起来
I go and visit her, we both get arrested.
听起来糟糕吗  兄弟
Is that bad enough for you, "bro"?
该你了  除非你难以启齿
Your turn, unless you're too tough to share.
霸天虎发射了一枚火箭
Decepticon fired a rocket.
父母当时在家  我没有
Parents were home, I wasn't.
没办法  我只能被送去寄养
No way I was going to foster.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, little guy.
你可真沉
You're heavy!
你得走了  你不能呆在这
You gotta go. You can't stay here.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧
Fine.
我早上会回来的
I'll bounce in the morning.
好吧  听着  你要是饿了  我这里有冷冻披萨卷饼
Great. Look, if you're hungry, I got some frozen pizza burritos.
冰箱里可能还有些零食
There might be some Smucker's in the fridge.
我会告诉所有人你在哪里
And tell everyone where you are.
嘿  我是被一个12岁的小孩威胁了吗
Hey, am I being blackmailed by a 12-year-old?
14岁
Fourteen.
你还真是错过了大好的年华
You know, you're really missing out.
做一个小孩没什么不好  厉害小孩
'Cause it's okay to be a kid, Little J-Lo.
你认为自己是个狠角色吗
You think you're a bad-ass?
好吧  女汉子  突击测试
All right, tough guy, I got a pop quiz for you.
假设在Slant-6引擎上有个内联的能量晶体泄漏
Say you got an inline Energon leak on a Slant-6.
不把它修好  汽车人能量就会流尽
Don't get it fixed, Autobot's about to bleed out.
你有30秒时间  现在回答  你会怎么做
You got 30 seconds. Now, what are you gonna do? Go.
好的  首先  变形金刚没有Slant-6引擎
All right. First of all, Transformers don't have a Slant-6.
那是克莱斯勒的发动机  古老的款式
That's a Chrysler engine, like way back in ancient history.
60年代末不算是古老
The late '60s are not ancient history.
对  但如果我要解决的是能量晶体泄漏
Yeah, but if I was fixing an Energon leak,
我会烧结干路并把中央流改路至那个  那个
I'd cauterize the artery and re-channel the central flow into the... The...
就是那个玩意  那个管子带有
The whatchamacallit, the tube with the...
- 一个小东西  - 对
- The doohickey thing. -Yeah.
不错
Not bad.
管好自己的嘴
Watch your mouth.
这东西在这多久了
How long has this been here?
它还在增长  是
It's growing. Yeah.
每天三米
Three meters a day.
六个角
Six horns.
六个角  对应六个地点
Six horns, six locations.
他们正在呈指数速度增长
And they're growing at an exponential rate.
外星人  不管他们是什么
Alien... Whatever they are.
中国人叫他们  地狱之角
Chinese call them "Horns from Hell."
天啊
My God.
赛博坦来了
Cybertron is coming.
什么
What?
我有17分钟的时间给总统做简报
I'll have 17 minutes to brief the President.
你给我带了什么
What do you got for me?
这是一个未建模的摄动质量
It's an unmodeled perturbation mass...
看这个  这东西居然飞得起来
Look at this. It's amazing this thing flies at all.
是某种颈部癌症吗
Is it some kind of neck cancer?
不  比那更糟
No. It's much worse than that.
是由一个以现速为0.1倍光速的行星大小物体
It's a gravitational anomaly caused by a planet-sized object
引起的引力异常
with a current velocity of 1/10th light speed.
净是书呆子用语  是个威胁吗
That's some geek stuff. Is it a threat?
如果你给我
If you just give me...
不  我还得吃午饭  不
No, I got a lunch. No.
不  不是个威胁
No, it's not a threat.
威胁可能会致命
A threat might kill you.
但这个肯定会在三天之内令你殒命
This will kill you in three days.
你多重
How much do you weigh?
严格地来说  你是超重了吗
Are you technically considered overweight?
不会  重量都来自于我身上的零件
No. It's just all my gear.
就像是在五磅重的袋子里  装上了10磅重的玩意儿
It's like somebody packed 10 pounds of shit in a five-pound sack.
不  他是个大块头的汽车人
No, he's a chunky Autobot.
能不能别弄了
You wanna stop that?
探长  拿出卫星电话
Hound, pull up the sat phone.
我把信号通过葡萄牙  伊斯坦布尔  和加德满都转接了
I'm bouncing a signal through Portugal, Istanbul and Katmandu.
你有20秒  老大
You got 20 seconds, chief.
- 哎呦  - 非得这样吗
- Whoops. - Really?
小变形金刚太烦人
Infestation of puppy transformers.
这里是个大孩子的天地
This here's a big boy zone.
你好
Hello?
你好  爸爸
Hello? Dad?
听着  我知道你不能跟我讲话
Look, I know... I know you can't talk to me
或是回答我
or say anything back.
但你可以听我说
But you can listen.
我会一直重复  直到你听我的话为止
I'm gonna say what I always say until you hear me.
你不需要拯救世界
You don't need to save the world.
你需要找个女朋友
You need a frigging girlfriend.
无论你在哪里  我都不希望你孤零零的死去
Wherever you are, I don't want you to die alone.
我也知道通话只剩五秒钟  所以
And I know you only got five seconds left, so...
我很好  我很安全
I'm fine, I'm safe.
而且我爱
And I love...
时间再长  他们就会追踪到我们的位置
Any longer, they'd have snagged our location.
你是个好父亲  凯德  别忘了
You're a hell of a father, Cade. Don't forget it.
该死  我爸爸从来不给我打电话
Hell, my dad never called me.
我们把它叫做深潭
We call it the Tank.
他喜欢这里
He likes it down here.
这就是我处理黑暗事物的地方
This is where I deal with the dark shit.
霸天虎似乎和我们一样对这些建筑感兴趣
Decepticons seem just as interested in these structures as we are.
这是在西伯利亚拍摄的
Pred snapped this in Siberia.
在世界上六个角的地方都发现了他的踪迹
He's been seen at all six horn locations around the world.
身份已经确定  是威震天
ID confirmed. Megatron.
听听这个  他与变形金刚应对部队联系
And get this. He made contact with TRF.
劫持了两名中情局官员  说他想要谈判
Snatched up two CIA case officers. Said he wants to negotiate.
和他  他想要什么
With him? What the hell does he want?
释放他指定的外星伙伴
Certain alien associates of his released.
联系人身份已经核实
Scheduled contact is ID'd and cleared.
确认  人质安全
Confirmation. Hostages are clear.
只要美军部队监视他的一举一动
The Department of Justice has okayed it
司法部门就没有异议
so long as the US military watches his every move.
你要保持警惕  因为他不是我们的朋友
You're gonna be on point, because he is not our friend.
你知道他们通常先杀谁吗
You know who they always kill first?
律师
Lawyers.
我们之前在紧急关头曾和这个恶魔做过交易
We've made deals with the devil before during times of crisis.
如果我们过不了这关
If we're gonna get through this,
我们就只能敞开大门
we have got to open the door
让怪物进来
and let the monsters inside.
那里有一种拥有超乎想像能量的武器
There is a weapon out there of unimaginable power.
是对我们生存的威胁
A threat to our very existence.
而威震天可以带我们找到它
And Megatron can lead us to it.
我认识你吗  人类
Do I know you, human?
- 我想要我的队员  - 告诉我名字
-I want my crew! -Give me names!
- 莫霍克  - 莫霍克
- Mohawk. - Mohawk?
怎么了  伙伴们  兄弟  我现在就想杀了你
What up, fellas? Man, I want to kill you right now.
但我还是之后再杀你吧
But I'ma kill you later.
过一会一定把你们都杀了
Definitely gonna kill y'all mofos later.
- 他没问题  - 好的
-He's cleared! -All right.
骇客
Dreadbot.
骇客  参与银行抢劫
Dreadbot. In for bank robbery.
故意伤人  谋杀
Aggravated assault. Murder.
双重谋杀  三重谋杀  九人死亡
Double murder. Triple murder. Nine dead.
根本没拿钱  不行
Didn't even take the money. No.
我们不能让他出来  不行
We're not letting him out, no.
什么
What?
我的意思是  但我们可以变通一下
I mean, but we can be flexible.
如果他戴着定位追踪器  就可以
If he wears a GPS tracker, it's fine.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
好吧
Okay.
氮气宙斯
Nitro Zeus.
宝贝  终于自由了
Baby, free at last!
感谢威震天  终于自由了
Thank Megatron, I'm free at last!
谢谢  会想你的  提姆
Thank you. Gonna miss you, Tim.
多谢你的招待  布拉德
Thank you for your hospitality, Brad.
我知道你住在哪  恩里克
I know where you live, Enrique.
替我跟你妻子问好
Say hello to your wife for me.
但是政府要求他不能出郡
But the government requests that he does not leave the county.
- 我们是认真的  - 好吧
- And we're serious about that. - Okay.
好吧
Okay.
最后但同样重要的  狂战士
And last but not least, Berserker.
我要吃了你的脑子
I'll suck your brains!
- 绝对不行  - 是啊  不行
- Absolutely not. - Yeah. No.
不  不  有限制的  重挑一个
No. No. There are limits. Pick again.
突袭
Onslaught.
你们需要个大点的门
You need a bigger door!
让我得向上面汇报一下
Let me run that up the flag pole real quick.
我只需要打个电话
I just got to call someone.
好极了  谢谢  可以  可以
Great, thank you. Yes. Yes!
走  快走
Go. Go.
你到底想做什么  威震天
What do you really want, Megatron?
跟所有人一样  人类
What anyone wants, human.
回家
To go home.
嗯  对我来说没问题
Yeah, that'd be all right with me, too.
威震天  他要的是耶格尔有的东西
Megatron, he's after something Yeager has.
一个能够帮助他们找到这个武器的东西
Something they need to help find this weapon.
我们会让霸天虎做脏活
We're gonna let those Decepticons do our dirty work.
照我预想  他们会得到耶格的藏身处坐标
On my go, they'll be given Yeager's hideout coordinates.
你要追踪威震天的一举一动
You track Megatron every step.
拿到武器
Take the weapon.
然后我会灭了他
And then I'm taking his ass out.
没有恐惧  没有憎恨  没有愤怒
No fear. No hate. No anger.
嘿  大伙
Hey, guys.
起床了  早上好
Rise and shine. Top of the morning!
废了老鼻子劲逮住的这些霸天虎
Broke our asses bagging these Decepticons.
现在让他们出去吗
Now they let them out?
到底发生什么了  伦诺克
What's really going on, Lennox?
机密
Classified.
把你的队伍管好
Just run your team.
今天
Today,
我们将进行猎捕
we hunt.
又是阳光明媚又无聊的一天
Another glorious, boring day.
战机空中待命
Air's gonna be on station.
利用红外光电传感器监视这些家伙的一举一动
We're gonna have all EOIR sensors on these guys as they move.
飞行编队  行进时注意战术机动
Flight, push tactical when airborne.
我要求空中作战部队配合这次运输
I want air ops locking down this transport.
时刻盯紧霸天虎
Decepticons in sight 100%.
已经把耶格的位置发送给霸天虎
Decepticons have just been given Yeager's location.
独眼巨人  霸天虎正接近废垃圾场的目标
Cyclops. Decepticons approaching junkyard target.
你绑着的是霸天虎的手臂吗
You strapping on a Decepticon arm?
完美
Perfecto.
他之前是个丑陋的小机器人
Well, he was an ugly little robot.
你看起来像个战士  叽叽
You look like a warrior, Sqweeks.
很帅
Muy guapo.
好了  大黄蜂
Here goes, Bee.
任你处置
Just do whatever you want.
嘿  Z  过来处理一下真正的机器人
Hey, Z, come on over here and work on a real bot.
医生  来吧  医生
Doc, come in, Doc.
对了
That's it.
不是  你左边第三个
No, third one on your left.
不  等下  你左边  这里
No. Wait. Your left. Right here.
我知道我在干什么  别催我
I know what I'm doing. Don't rush me.
嘿  心平气和些  好吗
Hey, calm the temper, okay?
你以为他喜欢这样吗
Think he likes this?
这种感觉像是在看牙医
It's like being in a dentist's chair.
你喜欢牙医吗  不
Do you like the dentist? No.
探长说你只能听她说话
Hound said you can only listen to her.
你女儿  你不能回答
Your daughter. You can't talk back.
他可真是大嘴巴
He's got a big mouth.
他说如果你打了  他们就可以从什么地方的什么电脑里
Said if you do, they can voice match you
做声音匹配来追踪你
from some computer somewhere and track you down.
这就是我们生活的世界
Well, that's the world we live in.
你想跟她说些什么
What would you say to her?
天天刷牙  努力学习
Brush your teeth, work hard.
远离所有乐队里的男孩  尤其是鼓手
Stay away from any boy in a band, especially a drummer.
对  鼓手最差劲了  还都很蠢
Yeah, drummers are the worst, not to mention stupid!
还有DJ  都是纯傻逼
And DJs? Real dickheads.
得了吧
Come on.
我们之间有个习惯  有个说法  经常反复说
We had a thing. All right? A saying, back and forth.
她经常会问我  爸  你明天准备做什么
She'd always ask me, "Dad, what are you doing tomorrow?"
我会说  明天再说
And I'd say, "I'll figure it out tomorrow."
看上去你的明天不多了啊  耶格
Looks to me like you're running out of tomorrows, Yeager.
她就会这样说
That's just what she'd say.
好了  黄蜂
Okay, Bee.
大功告成
Done.
来  哥们  坐起来  咱们听听
Come on, buddy, sit up. Let's hear it.
来
Come on.
你的真实的声音  第一次啊  老兄  喊出来
Your real voice. For the first time, buddy. Belt it out.
太激动了
This is so exciting.
不  这特么不是我的声音
No. This isn't my damn voice.
我非得杀了他  黄蜂
I'm gonna kill him, Bee.
这太扯淡了
This is such bullshit.
不行  我不会放弃的
Okay, you know what? I'm not giving up.
好吗  有朝一日你会用自己的声音说话的
All right? You're gonna speak with your own voice one day.
交易员是个大傻逼
Daytrader is a punk-ass bitch.
凯德  那个代码
Cade. That... That code.
有人来了
There's somebody coming.
该死
Shit!
收割者在监视垃圾场
Reaper has eyes on junkyard.
已确定首领身份
We have PID on Kingfish.
停  这是保护区
Halt! This is protected land!
六十秒后撤离  快行动
Sixty seconds to evac! Let's move!
独眼  敌方首领要逃了
Cyclops, it appears Kingfish is on the move.
他们知道了
They know.
我们暴露了  同志们  我们要马上撤了
We're blown, guys! We gotta roll out now!
那些是联调局的
Hey, those are the Feds.
我见到政府的人一眼能认出来
I know the government when I see the government.
能拿多少武器就拿多少武器
Grab as many weapons as you can.
我不能去监狱  我不能去监狱啊大哥
I'm not going to jail. I can't go to jail, man.
这是现实  快走
Hey! This is the real world. Okay? Let's go!
我不能去监狱  我太瘦了
I can't go to jail. I'm too skinny for jail.
我都举不了重的
I can't even lift weights.
黄蜂  快撤
Bee, let's move!
交给我  不要拦着我
Give me this one. You definitely gimme this one.
这个可要给他们好看
This will mess somebody up good.
快走吧  凯德  我给你争取一点时间
Roll out of here, Cade. I'm gonna buy you some time.
别逞英雄  探长  我们现在就走
Don't be a hero, Hound. We're out of here now!
等等
Wait! Wait!
我天生就是英雄
Hell, I was born a hero.
你不能离开我
You're not leaving me!
你离开了我  他们就要把吱吱带走了
You leave me, they take Sqweeks.
别管吱吱了  他能生存下来
Leave Sqweeks! He's a survivor.
威震天  他们走了
Megatron, they got up out of here.
很不幸啊  我还指望敲几颗脑袋呢
Unfortunate 'cause I was looking to knock some heads.
末日将近  我的叛徒老朋友
The end is near, my old treacherous friend.
你不能亲眼见到太遗憾了
What a shame you'll be unable to see it.
来尝尝这个  你个小婊砸
Come and get some, you little bitch!
朝你赶过去了  伦诺克
Coming your way, Lennox.
我们把它们围起来  他们会保护自己的
We box these things in, they will protect themselves.
我们等着瞧吧
Yeah, we'll see.
去战术位置  快走
Tactical positions, let's go!
你也是  胖子  别让他们看见  快点
You, too, knuckle-dragger. Stay out of sight. Come on.
霸天虎要来了
Decepticons are coming.
我们都清楚要藏在哪了
All right. We all know our hiding places.
这是什么  这个跟踪器直接把他们带向了我们
What's this? The tracker brought them right to us.
- 你什么时候才能长大啊  - 妹的
- When are you going to grow up? - Dang it.
目标在四公里之外
Target is four klicks away.
他们进入了一个废弃的小镇
They just entered an abandoned town.
快走  走走走走
Let's go. Out! Out! Out! Out!
喂
Hey!
耶格手上有重要资料  只能逮捕
Yeager's got vital intel. Detain only.
变形金刚反应部队的任务  不要挡道
TRF operation. Stay out of my way.
那些是我的人
Those were my men.
外面的事情太可怕了
Hey, there is some scary shit going on out there.
至少让我拿着我的冲击枪吧
I'd like to at least keep my blaster.
今天不行  我们得按照计划行动
Not today. We're sticking to the plan.
整个镇子都被监听了
The whole town is wired and rigged.
你  坐下  现在  不要动
You! Sit down. Now. Stay put.
提醒你一下  我们估计要进监狱了
Just a heads up. We're probably going to jail,
所以试着习惯一下吧
so try getting used to that.
他们来了
Here they come.
汽车人  准备好
Autobots, get ready.
凯德  你介意不介意我先走了
Hey, Cade, you mind if I bail?
我下令之前不要攻击
Don't attack until I say.
霸天虎到街上了
Yeah, Decepticons is in the streets.
- 我感觉一场大战来了  - 我现在就把你们杀光
- I feel a fight coming. - I'ma kill y'all right now.
搜索这个镇子
Search this town.
他在这里
He's here.
我要给你们点颜色看看
I'm letting y'all know what we came to do.
过来
Get over here!
看这个蓝色的甲虫一样的小傻逼玩意
Look at that little blue beetle-looking mofo.
看这个丑东西
Look at this little ugly dude.
你仿佛浸没在他们的臭气中  恶心
You are awash in their repulsive scent. Disgusting.
- 喂  - 黄蜂  阻止她
- Hey! - Bee, stop her.
放下他
Put him down!
不不不不不
No. No, no, no, no.
她过来了  看她麻花辫一摇一摇的霸气劲
Here she go. Look at her, walking all strong with pigtails.
下地狱吧
Go to hell!
这个星球就是地狱
This planet is hell.
你胳膊上那是什么
What's that on your arm?
- 放下他  - 妈的
- Put him down! - Shit!
你以为我怕你吗  傻逼
You think I'm afraid of you, cabron?
- 嘿  停下  - 凯德·耶格
- Hey, stop! - Cade Yeager.
我需要那个护符
I need that talisman!
我们不搞这种自杀式行动
We don't do this kamikaze shit.
你想跑过去朝一个霸天虎大喊大叫吗
You wanna go out there and start screaming at a Decepticon?
抓住那些可憎的生物
Get those vile beings.
我去抓他们
I'm on 'em!
我负责腿
I got the leg!
打到你了
Gotcha!
还有他的胖脑袋
And his fat head.
不能比这更棒了
Don't get any better than that.
马上撤退
Drift, now!
霸天虎们  撤退
Decepticons, retreat!
怂包
Chickens!
这个计划完蛋了
That plan went to shit.
你就这一个计划吗
That's the only plan you got?
蹲下  蹲下  蹲下
Get down, get down, get down!
那是什么
What are those?
变形金刚反应部队
TRF.
我们得进屋  来  跑起来
We gotta get inside. Come on. Run.
这些人应该去抓捕恐怖分子
This is supposed to hunt terrorists,
不是美国纳税人
not tax-paying Americans!
也不是说我纳税  但是
Not that I pay taxes, but...
老威  威老天
Yo, Meg! M-tron!
别玩了  快点  这里只有我吗
Stop playing. Come on. Am I the only one in here?
这可不对
This ain't right.
我们在这里很安全
We're safe in here.
总有一个领头的
There's always one in charge.
像在芝加哥那时候  像妈妈一样的人
Just like back in Chicago, like a mother.
走走走
Go, go, go!
快跑
Run!
走走走
Move, move, move!
躲在那个屋里
Hide in that room!
快快快
Come on, come on, come on!
我没穿兜帽就为了不被枪击
I left the 'hood to not get shot
现在我被子弹袭击
and now I'm getting shot.
这是史上最差的工作
This is the worst job ever.
这个工作有医保吗
Does this job even have healthcare?
没有  是吧
It doesn't, do it?
你试试自己治疗子弹伤
You try treating a bullet wound by yourself.
小心
Watch out!
快跑
Run! Run!
躲起来  躲起来
Hide! Hide!
启动脸部识别
Facial mapping engaged.
你死定了
You're a dead man.
完了  这里还有一个
Shit. There's another one.
- 交给我  - 你在干什么
- I got this. - What are you doing?
它用的是脸部识别
It's using facial recognition.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
- 待在我后面  - 什么
- Stay behind me. - What?
- 吉米  不要  - 包在我身上  待在我后面
- Jimmy J, don't! - I got this. Get behind me.
- 不要这样  - 待在我后面
- Don't do it. - Get behind me.
这不是好主意
It's a bad idea!
该死
Shit.
天啊  你还好吧
My gosh. Are you okay?
凯德  我只想说  我爱你  老哥
Cade, I just want to tell you, I love you, man.
啥
What?
这个工作和我想象的不一样  但我很感激
This job wasn't what I thought, but I appreciate everything.
- 你在干什么  - 我要死了
- What are you doing? - I'm dying!
就是个沙包  大哥
It was only a beanbag, dude.
没有洞吗
There's no hole?
没有洞  没有血  什么都没有
There's no hole, there's no blood, no nothing.
- 没有洞  - 你能站起来吗
- There's no hole. - Will you get up?
别逞英雄了
Stop trying to act like a hero.
就是个沙包  这玩意儿疼的像个子弹  老哥
It was a beanbag? That shit hurt like a bullet, man!
感觉它好像直接穿过我了
I felt it go through me!
来  那边的建筑
Come on, that building right there!
总得有一个领头的
There's always one in charge!
好了  我们干掉老大  我们就能他们都干掉
All right, we take out the big one, we're gonna take them all out.
快点快点快点  快快  他们来了
Come on, come on, come on. Hurry, hurry, they're coming.
- 天哪  一个矮精灵  - 你特么是谁
- My God! A leprechaun. - Who the hell are you?
矮精灵很小  浑身绿色  还是爱尔兰的
Leprechauns are tiny, green and Irish,
这话太冒犯了
and that is offensive.
你看什么  小姑娘
What are you looking at, little girl?
你看什么
What are you looking at?
你好  凯德大人  我被派来接你
Hello. Master Cade, I have been sent to collect you.
- 接我  - 正确
- Collect me? - That is correct.
你接个屁
You're not collecting shit.
哥  慢点
Man! Slow down!
好啊  你想来玩硬的
So, you want to play rough.
不  不  凯德
No! No! Cade!
该死
Shit!
- 凯德  凯德  - 抓紧
- Cade! Cade! - Hold on!
你看到了吗  等一下
Did you see that? Hang on!
我太笨了
I am so clumsy!
- 他还活着吗  - 抓住了
-Is he still alive? -Hold on!
他还活着吗
Is he still living?
不  他要死了
No, he's going to die!
主人  这不是我的错
My lord, this is not my fault,
他直接从电梯里冲出去了
but he just burst out of the elevator.
十层楼啊
Ten stories.
老天
My God.
你还有备用计划吗  先生
Did you have a backup plan, sir?
- 他还活着吗  - 我不知道  他就直接飞走了
- Did he live? - I don't know! He just flew!
大人  扯掉人的一只的胳膊
My lord, rip an arm off a human
蔷突崛文阒?
你怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
你个小虫子
You little gnats.
你在这儿啊  真高兴看到你还活着
There you are. Good to find you alive!
就好像什么都没有发生
Just like nothing happened.
- 让我把你弄得体面点  - 喂  干啥
- Let's make you presentable. - Hey! Come on!
干干净净亮晶晶
Shiny, spick and span.
- 滚蛋  管家婆  - 好了
- Back off, Jeeves! - There.
- 你已经开始变好看了  先生  - 你是谁
- You look better already, sir. - Who are you?
我的名字叫长老  先生  我是为了那个而来的
My name is Cogman, sir. And I am here because of that.
那个是跟着你来的
And that is here because of you.
它不会离开你  直到你的完成使命
It will not leave you until your quest is fulfilled.
你被选中了
You have been chosen.
你什么意思  选中
What do you mean, "chosen"?
我可以解释这一切  只要你能跟我走
I will explain everything if you'll kindly come with me.
凯德  这个盗版C-3PO是怎么回事
Cade, what's with this C-3PO rip-off?
休斩来使
Don't kill the messenger
否则来使斩了你
or the messenger will kill you.
恐怕这些乱子都是你的错
Now then, I'm afraid all this ballyhoo is on your account.
如果你想救你的朋友  你就离开他们
If you want to save your friends, you will leave them.
不要和那个矮精灵说话
Hey, don't talk to that leprechaun!
怎么  然后就跟一个疯子忍者管家走吗
What, and run off with some crazy ninja butler?
你不在的时候你的朋友会安全的
Your friends will be safe in your absence.
你在的时候反而不安全
In your presence, unsafe.
你的重要性你自己的想象不到
You are more important than you can possibly imagine.
有人需要你  先生
You are needed, sir.
非常紧急
Urgently.
我的主人很喜欢说
My master is fond of saying
生活中的所有重要的决定
that all the important decisions in life
经常取决于一个瞬间
often come down to just one moment.
你不会有事的  你是我的家人了
You're gonna be all right. You're family now.
他们会照顾你的  我保证
They're gonna take care of you, I promise.
飞机在等着了  我们要去英格兰
The plane is waiting. We are going to England.
黄蜂
Bee?
听好了  阳光小姑娘  现在听我的指挥
Listen up, Little Miss Sunshine, I'm in charge now.
只是不要指望我给你将睡前故事
Just don't expect any bedtime stories.
欢迎来到福尔根号
Welcome to Air Folgan.
请系好安全带  气流会致命的
Please strap in. Turbulence can kill.
此次航班上不会提供零食
There will be no snack service on this flight,
没有饮料  没有娱乐
no drinks, no fun.
跟踪耶格  他在大西洋上方了
Tracking Yeager. He's over the pond right now.
找了好久  不过卫星找到了他
It took some finding, but sats have him.
威震天和他的人去英国了
Megatron and crew are bearing down on the UK.
耶格也是  这不可能是巧合
So is Yeager. It's no coincidence.
你马上和你的队伍空降到英国
I want you airborne with your team to the UK ASAP.
接电话  接电话
Pick up. Pick up.
喂
Yeah?
- 别挂  - 又是你
- Don't hang up! - It's you again.
我告诉你了  你什么都给不了我  消失吧
I've told you, you have nothing to offer. Get lost.
我求你个事  福尔根  我想自己做  但做不到
I need a favor, Folgers. I'd do it myself, but I can't.
你做过古巴的飞机吗
You ever fly a Cuban airplane?
是1940年代的飞机  飞行员也是
They're from the 1940s. So are the pilots.
凯尔经
Book of Cyber-Kells.
被我找到了
I found it.
那个古书  不可能
The ancient book? Impossible.
只要你认识正确的清洁工就可能  我认识很多
Not when you know the right janitor. And I know many.
这本书是存在的  几个世纪没人见过了
The book exists. Unseen for centuries.
书页会在室温下分解
Pages that literally dissolve at room temperature,
材质是什么古老品种的羊宝还是什么的
made from some old kind of goat scrotum or something.
三位一体博物馆  今天下午四点
Trinity Library. Today, 4:00 p.m.
如果你想要知道这一切的结局就到那去
Be there if you want to know how it all ends.
物体确认为地外行星赛博坦星球
Object confirmed as exoplanet Cybertron.
距离撞击还有两天  七个小时
Two days, seven hours to impact.
擎天柱  是时候让你知道真相了
Optimus, it is time you knew the truth.
那个你称为地球的地方
The place you call Earth
有另一个名字叫做  宇宙大帝
has another name. Unicron.
地球  宇宙大帝
Earth... Unicron?
赛博坦古老的敌人
Cybertron's ancient enemy.
没错
Yes.
你要去杀了他
You are going to kill him.
利用我的法杖  我们将抽干宇宙大帝的生命
With my staff, we will drain the very life from Unicron.
- 地球会死去  - 没错
- Earth will die... -Yes.
你的世界会重生
And your world will be reborn,
复仇擎天柱
Nemesis Prime.
我会击败所有挡路之人
I will fight anyone who stands in my way.
外星角状物还在不断增大
The alien horns are still growing,
其中一些已经达到了400米
some of them reaching 400 meters.
又是外星人的垃圾新闻
More alien rubbish.
薇薇安  你找到男朋友没有
Have you found a man yet, Viviane?
- 没有  - 太可惜了
- No. - So sad.
你真的应该好好找找
You should really look in here.
我是说  这有不少广告  有一部分很有吸引力
I mean, there are lots of adverts, some of them very tempting.
这个在找一个BBW  我不知道那是什么意思吗
This one's looking for a BBW. I don't know what that is.
- 那是种车  亲  - 好吧
- It's a car, dear. - Right.
大美女
Big Beautiful Woman.
是吗  谁知道呢
Is it? Who knew?
看看分类信息栏
Looking at the classifieds!
这个有它自己的地牢
This one's got its own dungeon.
太好了  我喜欢地牢
Great! I love dungeons!
看见没  这太合适了  不是吗
See, that's perfect for you, isn't it?
那些老物件  你会喜欢的
All that old stuff, you'd love that.
历史正在被改写  而你却想要谈论男人
History is being rewritten and you want to talk about a man.
或者女人
Or a woman.
海伦阿姨
Aunt Helen.
女追女  这不是嘛
"Women Seeking Women." Here we go.
你可以问问我工作上的事
You could ask me about my work.
我们为什么要这么做
Why would we do that?
不过是些旧书罢了
I mean, it's just dusty old books.
现在我有点盼望世界末日的到来了
Now I welcome the end of days!
我只是希望你能找到像你父亲这样对的人
What's so terrible about me wanting you
这有什么不好吗
to have what I had with your father?
他是个混球
He was an ass.
你知道父亲没有什么吗
Do you know what Father didn't have?
一样他挚爱的圆桌骑士都有
The one thing that his beloved Knights of the Round Table
而他却极其缺乏的东西
had in spades and he was utterly lacking?
信用
Honor.
这我无法反驳
You can say that again.
你要是抱怨够了死人
If you can stop loathing a dead man long enough,
你也许会想去他的书房看看
you might want to have a look in his study.
那堆垃圾
All that rubbish.
你可能想要留下几件
There might be something you want to keep.
别碰那个
Do not touch that!
抱歉  爸爸
Sorry, Daddy.
我什么都不想要
I don't want anything.
让学校都拿走吧
Tell the university to take the lot.
弗尔根伯爵十二世
"The 12th Earl of Folgan
急切地邀请您于此刻
"urgently requests your presence at High Tea
前去喝下午茶
"this very moment."
停下
Stop!
闪开  让路
Move! Move!
天呐  抱歉
God! Sorry!
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
拜托  女士  别那么做
Please, mademoiselle, don't do that.
- 什么  - 我是热破
- What? -Je m'appelle Hot Rod.
真要命  你也是他们中的一员
Christ alive, you're one of them!
到后面去  安静点  别再打我了
Back! Be quiet! Do not hit me again!
所以你是哪一个
So, which bloody bot are you, then?
声波  震荡波
Soundwave? Shockwave?
至少告诉我我是被个知名的变形金刚绑架了
At least tell me that I've been abducted by one of the famous ones.
我比他们所有人都要优秀得多
I am so much better than all of them!
救命  我被绑架了
Help! I'm being kidnapped!
女士  请坐下
Mademoiselle, sit down!
救命  喂
Help! Yes, yes, hello!
喂  兰博基尼
Hello, Lamborghini!
能帮帮忙吗
Would you help?
- 抱歉  我被绑架了  - 疯子
- Sorry, I've just been kidnap... - Nuts!
我喜欢这辆车
I love this car!
多佛白崖
The White Cliffs of Dover.
好女孩  乖
That's a good girl. Good girl.
好姑娘  来  真乖
Good girl. Come on. There's a good girl.
我们有客人了
We have guests!
你这是什么毛病
What's the matter with you?
该死  我的零件都掉了
Shit! My bits are falling off.
笨蛋
Idiot!
你们好啊
Hello there!
什么鬼
What the hell?
好姑娘
Good girl.
主人  这家伙就是个楞头青
Master, he's a complete knucklehead.
对于刚才的事我感到很抱歉  你看
I'm awfully sorry about that, but, you see,
他以为现在还是1918或者1914年  大概就那段时间
he thinks it's still the year 1918 or 1914. Something like that.
太令人伤感了
So sad.
第一次世界大战什么的
World War I and all that stuff.
第一次马恩河战役  索姆河战役
I mean... Battle of the Marne, Battle of the Somme,
第二次马恩河战役  巴雪戴尔战役
Battle of the Marne, Battle of Passchendaele.
壕沟与泥泞中
Trenches and mud and death
到处都是血迹和成堆的尸体  着实令人伤感
and gore and all that. It's terribly sad.
离蒂珀雷里还远  家乡遥遥无际
"It's a long way to Tipperary, it's a long way to go."
那真的是太残酷了
Yeah, but it's... It's terrible!
太惨烈了  你知道吗  但是当时
I mean, so sad, you know? But then, I mean...
不是吗  我是说  这种迟发性的
Isn't it? I mean, this late onset of, well...
机器人痴呆
Robot dementia.
得了之后可不好过
It's not at all pretty.
我不知道你那烟管里抽得是什么
I don't know what you're smoking in that pipe, man, but...
这里到底是怎么回事
What's going on here?
你是把我拉到什么
Did you drag me to some
变形金刚的养老院了吗
Transformer retirement home?
听着  最好有人能给我解释一下  不然我可要走了
Look, somebody better start talking, or I'm outta here.
好的
Okay.
大黄蜂
Bumblebee?
我们只在我小时候见过一面
We only met when I was a little boy in short pants.
我大概那么高
I must have been that tall.
也许高点  也许矮点  我记不得了
Maybe taller. Or maybe shorter, I can't remember.
但从不会忘记别人的长相
But never forget a face.
大黄蜂  你认识这个家伙吗
Bee, you know this guy?
我们来看看这个东西
Let's have a look at this thing.
可以吗  这很有趣
Please. Very interesting.
没错
Yes.
你保守这个秘密这么长时间  知道那是真的
You keep a secret for so long, knowing it to be true,
然而  内心深处
and yet, deep down inside,
你却产生疑问
you begin to wonder,
我的人生被荒废了吗
"Has my life been wasted?"
你有没有过那样的感觉  凯德先生
Have you ever felt like that, Mr. Cade?
叫我凯德就好
It's just Cade.
听着  老前辈  我现在可没那么多耐心陪你猜谜语
Look, old timer, I don't have a ton of patience for riddles right now.
没错  但是你想要知道  不是吗  老兄
Yes, but you want to know, don't you, "dude,"
他们为什么不断来到这里
why they keep coming here.
来到地球  对吗
To Earth. Right?
我很欣赏掐准时机的人
I do so love perfect timing.
多靓的车啊
What a bitchin' car she is!
不  不  别跑  小姐
No, no, no, little lady.
你为什么非要这个样子呢  为什么【法】
Why do you have to be like that? Pourquoi?
这是因为她被绑架了
So, is this a kidnapping sort of situation
还是因为 她第一次见变形金刚
or her first Transformer experience?
其实二者都有
It's both, really.
别再打我了
Do not hit me again!
但是她的战逃反应很不错
But she does have a rather nice fight-or-flight response.
她可真难搞
She's very difficult.
我叫埃德蒙·伯顿  弗尔根伯爵十二世
My name is Edmond Burton, 12th Earl of Folgan.
维特维坎家族团最后一名在世的成员
Last surviving member of the Order of the Witwiccans.
还好吗
What's up?
他非要倚在那吗
Does he have to loom like that?
惹什么
"Ut" what?
热泼
"Ut rut"?
热破
Hot Rod.
他有法国口音
It's his French accent.
他是法国人吗
Is he French?
不  他只是喜欢那个口音
No, he just likes the accent.
不  不  不  我讨厌这口音  但是我摆脱不了它
No, no, no! I hate the accent! But I can't get rid of it.
我改不掉这个口音了
I'm stuck with the accent.
他是位军人  薇薇安小姐
He's a soldier, Miss Viviane.
他向你的父亲宣誓要保护你
He swore an oath to your father to protect you.
你爸可真不错
Some dad you got there.
那车真不错  要我说  你开着他
That is a nice ride. I mean, you can roll right up
去白金汉宫都不成问题
to Buckingham Palace in that thing.
好了 你  美国佬  闭嘴
Okay, you, American man, shut it.
我来这是做什么的
What am I doing here?
- 是啊  为什么要把她请来  - 给你们介绍一下
- Yeah, why is she here? - Introductions.
这位是薇薇安·温布利小姐  牛津大学历史学硕士
Miss Viviane Wembly. Master of History, Oxford.
哲学博士   也是在牛津大学读的
Doctor of Philosophy, also Oxford.
文学博士  还是牛津大学的学位  我想想  还有别的吗
And Doctor of Letters, again Oxford, I think. Anything else?
不管怎样  认识一下凯德
Anyway, meet Cade.
耶格尔
Yeager.
凯德·耶格尔  我是个发明家
Cade Yeager. I'm an inventor.
你是个发明家
You're an inventor.
- 是的  我是  - 你都发明了什么
- Yes, I am. - What have you invented?
- 很多东西  - 比如呢
- A lot of things. - Like?
比如很多东西
Like a lot of things. Like...
- 你听过的  - 像是
- Things that you've heard of. - Like?
好吧  你将来会听说的
Well, things that you will have heard of, okay?
专利还在申请
Patents are pending.
别那个样子  啊是什么意思吗
Don't say that. What's "?
你知道么  我也能来那一套  我是英国人
You know, I could do that, too. "I'm English,
我酷到喜不形于色
"and I'm too cool for feelings."
怎么  我来这是为了
What, I've come here to be insulted
被一个穿着脱衣舞娘裙子拿了一沓学历证书的象牙塔小公主羞辱的吗
by some over-educated ivory-tower princess in a stripper dress?
脱衣舞娘
Stripper?
也就只有在美国受过良好教育被视为一种侮辱
Well, only in America is a finer education an insult.
如果我的裙子让你感到不适
And if my dress makes you feel uncomfortable,
那么也许我会把它脱下来
then maybe I could take it off.
好呀
Okay.
够了  你这个禽兽
That's enough!
- 你这人有什么毛病  - 不 不 不
- What's your problem? - No, no, no!
长老
Cogman?
要我把他的头拧下来吗
Shall I take his head off, madam?
很诱人的提议  但是  我能够维护自己的尊严
Tempting, but, I can defend my own honor.
但我很想捏断他的脖子
But I do so very much want to crush his windpipe.
矜持一点  长老  你必须学着控制你的脾气
Control, Cogman. You must learn to control that impulse.
把怒气转移到其它方面
Channel it into other things.
好的  伯爵
Yes, my lord.
像是铺床  做饭
Like making beds or cooking food.
抛光银器  我在努力了  伯爵
Polishing the silver. I am trying, my lord.
他是个头领战士  很少见的种类
He is a "Headmaster." A very rare breed.
这家伙疯了吧
That dude is disturbed, yeah?
极度邪恶  人格分裂那种的
Like, seriously evil. Like, split personality.
很好
Good.
长老  17C玻璃杯在哪  你打了吗
Cogman? Glass 17C is missing. Did you break it?
我给贵族当了700多年管家
I've been a butler for the aristocracy for 700 years.
没见过你这么难伺候的
You are the worst I've ever worked for!
这些是我的前任的画像
These were all my predecessors.
他们都是弗尔根家族的  这是我的姑奶奶
They're all Folgans. And that was my aunt there.
我的曾 曾 曾姑奶奶
My great-great... great-great aunt.
出于某些原因她把我的曾  曾叔祖父毒死了
She poisoned my great-great-great uncle for some reason.
她疯得要命  是个彻头彻尾的疯婆子
She was barking mad, she was an absolute bitch.
那边是我的祖父  阿洛伊修斯
There's my grandfather over there, Aloysius.
那是阿诺德  我的第三个堂兄
And that's Arnold, my third cousin.
他喝下水道的水  后来自杀了  他也疯得可以
He drunk sewage water, committed suicide. He was quite mad.
说实话  他们都挺疯的
They were all mad, really.
这上面有弹孔
There's bullet holes.
不  不  这是个坏脾气的家伙
No, no. Nasty critter.
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
就是它杀了希特勒  别惹他
That's the watch that killed Hitler. Don't screw with it.
这些都是维特维坎家族团的成员
These are all the Witwiccans.
在我们的鼎盛时期家族团相当成气候
In our halcyon days we were quite the club.
聚集了才华横溢的人  有探险家  科学家  艺术家  世界领袖
Brilliant minds, explorers, scientists, artists, world leaders.
文艺复兴的弄潮儿
Renaissance thrill seekers.
像是俄国女皇叶卡捷琳娜二世  俄国女皇
People like Catherine the Great, Empress of all Russia,
华盛顿将军
General Washington,
威廉·莎士比亚  英国女王伊丽莎白一世
William Shakespeare, Queen Elizabeth of England,
亚伯拉罕·林肯  弗雷德里克·道格拉斯
Abraham Lincoln, Frederick Douglass,
哈莉特·塔普曼  莱特兄弟
Harriet Tubman, the Wright Brothers,
乔托·迪·邦多纳  米开朗基罗  丘吉尔  爱因斯坦
Giotto, Michelangelo, Darwin, Churchill, Einstein,
斯蒂芬·霍金  亨利五世  列昂纳多·达·芬奇
Stephen Hawking, Henry V, Leonardo da Vinci,
牛顿  德·拉瓦锡  莫扎特  贝多芬  古斯塔夫·马勒
Newton, de Lavoisier, Mozart, Beethoven, Mahler,
艾德蒙·希拉里  泰迪·罗斯福  哥白尼
Edmund Hillary, Teddy Roosevelt, Copernicus,
特斯拉  伽利略
Tesla, Galileo.
他们都属于一个秘密的社团  如你所见
They all belonged to a secret society, you see.
全都齐聚一堂只为一个事业
All united in one cause.
保守变形金刚在地球上历史
To protect the secret history of Transformers.
的秘密
Here. On Earth.
这是一副维特维坎谱系图
Now, this is the Witwiccan family tree.
梅林  薇薇安娜
Merlin, Viviana.
可以向上追溯40代人
Goes back 40 generations.
到那边的桌子去  那里有张照片
Go over to that desk. There's a photograph there.
你的父亲也曾是成员之一
Your father was a member.
他非常希望告诉你这一点
He very much wanted to tell you that.
我自己的家族
And my own family had some...
也对此有所贡献
Small part in all this.
ZB-7
ZB-7.
看起来很像蜜蜂
That looks just like Bee.
的确如此  他跟随第一特遣部队作战
It is. He was attached to the Devil's Brigade.
非常强大的军事单位
Pretty vicious military unit.
帮助扭转了战局
Helped turn the tide of war, you know?
我们并非受邀而来
We're not invited.
- 大黄蜂还干过这些  - 没错
-  Bee? -Yeah.
但他那么和善
But he's so nice.
战争期间   在后方
Behind the lines, during the war,
人们对他有很多评价
they called him many things.
和善绝不是其中之一
"Nice" was never one of them.
一切都起始于公元484年
It all began in 484 AD,
亚瑟王和他的巫师  梅林
when King Arthur and his wizard, Merlin,
在巴登山大败萨克森部队
stared down and vanquished the Saxon hordes at Mount Badon.
那是他的剑和他的法杖
That's his sword and his mace there.
那是个传说
It's a myth.
是啊  每个传说  神话
Yeah, every legend, every myth,
每个篝火边口耳相传的故事
every story whispered around the campfire
都有一个合理的解释
has a logical explanation.
这我完全同意
With that I agree wholeheartedly,
但已经毫无逻辑可言了
but logic has left the building.
因为你在讲魔法
You're talking about magic.
怎么  你说会走路说话的兰博基尼是魔法吗
What, like your walking, talking Lamborghini?
任何足够超前的技术
"Any sufficiently advanced technology
都与魔法无异
"is indistinguishable from magic."
亚瑟·C·克拉克  厉害
Arthur C. Clarke. Impressive.
对  还包括那些没有学生贷款
Yeah. And count 'em, zero student loans,
博士  教授  哲人  不管你叫自己什么
Doctor, or Professor, Philosopher, whatever you call yourself.
全都是我的头衔
It's all of the above.
这地方
Now, this place was built
是建立在原始圆桌的基础上
around the original Round Table.
珀西瓦尔  高文  崔斯坦  兰斯洛特
Percival, Gawain, Tristan, Lancelot.
他们就坐在那
They sat right here.
十二人
Twelve in all.
在他们之后坐着十二位赛博坦人
And behind them sat the 12 who came from Cybertron.
我们为荣誉而战
We fight for honor.
为人类而战
We fight for the human race.
为人类的美好而战
For all that is good in mankind.
敬新朋旧友
To brothers old and brothers new!
没有牺牲就没有胜利
No sacrifice, no victory!
出现在卡米洛特的十二位外星骑士
Twelve alien knights who saw in Camelot
展现了人类最珍贵的品质
what the human race could be at its finest.
荣誉的竞赛
A race of honor.
长老
Cogman?
你又破坏气氛了
You ruined the moment again!
我只是想让气氛更恢弘
I was making the moment more epic.
安静点就行了
Just be quiet.
有什么毛病
What's the matter with you?
要是让我找到他脖子我一定掐死他
If I could find his neck, I'd strangle him.
这是亚瑟王的东西
This belonged to King Arthur himself.
传说最后的骑士在某天会注定
Now, legend held that one last knight would someday be chosen
接受使命为拯救世界顽强而战
and the struggle to save the world would begin.
看起来  凯德先生
It would appear, Mr. Cade,
你是最后的骑士
that that last knight is you.
什么
What?
你的意思是他穿越了整个宇宙就为了找我吗
You're saying he traveled the whole universe to find me?
不  不是特意来找你
No, not you specifically.
不是来找这个德州来的失败发明家
Not a failed inventor from the state of Texas.
才不是
No, God forbid.
停
Stop it!
怎么了
What?
你要是不停下
You know, if you don't stop it,
我会用一个小盒子装你送回赛博坦
I will send you back to Cybertron in a little tiny box.
我好怕怕
Scary.
我不是失败的发明家
I am not a failed inventor.
他要找的是符合骑士精神的人  凯德先生
No, he meant the qualities of a knight, Mr. Cade.
薇薇安小姐  骑士精神  请说一下
Miss Viviane, the qualities of a knight, if you please?
骑士精神是  纯净的心灵
Qualities of a knight, purity of heart,
勇猛  荣誉感  贞洁  正直
valor, honor, virtue, integrity.
我有这些品质
I have those.
最重要的是
And most importantly...
- 他是否纯贞  - 被人追吗
-Is he chaste? -Chased?
老兄  我被你那奇怪的伙计一直追
Dude, I was getting chased when your little weirdo buddy
直到把我带到这来
brought me over here on the plane.
纯贞
"Chaste."
纯  贞
C-H-A-S-T-E.
贞
"T."
禁欲
Celibate?
我知道  我只是逗你们
Yeah, I know... I was making a joke.
你以为我不会吗
You don't think I know how to spell?
- 我知道他的意思  - 当然了
-I know what he meant. -Sure you were.
不打打飞机吗  凯德先生
No whoopee, Mr. Cade?
很久没有了
It's been a while.
很久是多久  一周  一个月  一年
Well, how long's "a while"? A week? A month? A year?
不关你事
None of your business.
我们得问你这个问题
Well, we need to ask you the question.
很久就是很久
A while!
这又是英国人的毛病吗
Is that, like, another English thing?
不  只是我们好奇
No, no. Just a curious thing.
也许我守身如玉呢
Well, maybe I'm saving myself.
你为什么要守身如玉  老头
What are you saving yourself for, old age?
你这个英国女人  闭嘴
You, English lady, shut it.
这是什么  地图吗
What is this? Some sort of a map?
这桌子来自赛博坦
This table is from Cybertron.
这是我研究了一阵子的地图
It's a puzzle I've been working on for some time.
其实研究一生了
My entire life, actually.
这些字符是什么意思
And what do these glyphs say about it?
古赛博坦语
They're Olde Cybertronian.
从宇宙低声传来的咒语
A mantra whispered through the cosmos.
保护法杖
"Seglass ni Tonday."
等下
Wait a minute.
我听过
I heard that before.
船上的骑士说过  是什么意思
A knight on a ship. What does it mean?
用你最后一口气  保护好法杖
"With your dying breath, protect the staff."
这太荒唐了
Okay, this is ridiculous.
他们为它起了名字
They had their name for it.
我们也有
We have ours.
梅林之杖
The staff of Merlin.
外星人赠与给他的  融合了他的基因
Bequeathed to him by an alien race. Fused with his DNA.
因此只有他才有打开它里面外星力量的钥匙
So that only he would have the key to unlock its alien power.
也就是如今的
Or as they knew it in those days,
魔法
magic.
这只法杖葬在了梅林身边
The staff was buried with Merlin's body.
我们藏了一千年
A thousand years we've kept it hidden.
若是落入坏人手中
If it ever fell into the wrong hands, it would mean
我们身边爱着的一切便不就会毁灭
the imminent destruction of everything we know and love.
12位守护骑士合体变成了龙来保护它
The 12 Guardian Knights combined into a mighty dragon to protect it.
现在它陷入了大麻烦
And now it is in great danger.
威震天  他在找它
Megatron. He was after this.
所以大战要来临了
So the battle is upon us.
这就是他们在这的原因  为什么他们一直来地球
It is why they're here, why they keep coming to Earth.
我们必须在太迟之前拿走法杖
And we must claim the staff before it is too late.
等下  干嘛
Wait. We what?
只有一位梅林的直系后代
Only a direct descendant of Merlin himself
能够挥动这拥有绝对权力的法器
can wield this instrument of absolute power.
而你  薇薇安小姐
And you, Miss Viviane,
是梅林在地球上最后一位恣睢
are Merlin's last descendant here on Earth, and as such,
因此  你是我们最后的希望
you are our last hope.
等下  后退一点
Okay, wait. Go back.
你是说我和魔法师梅林有血缘关系吗
You're saying that I'm related to the wizard Merlin?
有点惊讶  是不是
Bit of a shock, isn't it?
只有你知道法杖在哪
Only you know the staff's location,
由你父亲传给你
imparted to you by your father.
他肯定会留下线索  对吧
He had to leave a clue, didn't he?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
看她这样似乎不知道法杖在哪
She doesn't have that "I know where the staff is" look.
听着  我父亲唯一告诉我的是
Listen, the only thing that my father imparted to me
离开他的书房
was to get out of his study.
两个世界碰撞  只有一个存活
"Two worlds colliding, only one survives."
这是你的原话  只是你下课了
Your words exactly. Only lecture time is over.
你就是为这而生
You were born for this.
这是他们来这之前自己星球的最后画面
This is the latest image of their world coming here.
而你们都挡了他们的路
And you're all that stand in its way.
所以你们必须快点找到法杖
So you'd better find that staff quickly.
快
Now!
变形金刚反应部队
TRF.
保卫封锁城堡
Surround the castle and lock it down.
军情六处和变形金刚反应部队来了
MI6 and TRF are here!
撤退  快
Move it! Go!
长老  带我去伦敦好吗
Cogman, get me to London, okay?
- 伪装车准备好了吗  - 快点
-The decoy car is ready? -Hurry along.
交给我
I got 'em boys!
快点  快走
Hurry, move! Quick, quick, quick!
大黄蜂带我们离开
Get us out of here, Bee.
快离开  我的武器能停止时间
Get out of here! My weapon will stop the time!
爱因斯坦估计都会被逗乐了  摸摸
Einstein would've been tickled pink. Foo-Foo!
快点  这边  这边走
Quick, this way, this way! Hurry!
霰弹枪  我要霰弹枪
Shotgun. I call shotgun.
直升机入境  可以安全降落
Inbound helos, you are clear to land.
伦诺克上校刚到
Colonel Lennox just hit the deck.
我是桑托斯  美国队长  有什么消息
This is Santos, Team Leader USA. What you got?
变形金刚反应部队飞艇上路了
TRF airship on the way.
在后面等我
Meet me around back, Bee.
我不会玩
I suck at this game!
你咬手指的时候就出卖了自己
When you bite your nails, you give everything away.
妈
Mum?
这是凯德
Everybody, this is Cade.
凯德  这是我家人
Cade, this is my family.
你好
Hello!
- 你好  - 凯德
-Hi. -Cade?
你好  我叫玛丽
Hello. I'm Marie.
你有地牢吗
Do you have a dungeon?
老天  手像个粗糙的老树皮
My goodness! Hands like rough old maple.
看着像木头一样强壮
He looks hard as wood.
别碰他  我去换衣服
Don't touch him. I'm gonna go and get changed.
我收到一通三位一体图书馆的愤怒清洁工来的电话
I got a call from a very irate janitor at Trinity Library.
你迟到了
You're late.
确实  如他们所说  陷入了小麻烦
We are, as they say, in a bit of a pickle.
现在别搞我
Do not mess with me at this moment!
天气很热  我脾气也很爆
It's hot, and I am on a short fuse.
快点  去图书馆
Quick! Get to the library!
追人的活让我压力很大
This chasing is stressing me out.
军情六处和变形金刚反应部队要找到我们了  我们得快点
MI6 and TRF are gonna find us. We got to hurry.
我父亲东西很多
My dad had a lot of stuff.
那找到法杖的地点
So, finding the staff's location...
是什么意思  我们在找  什么
What does that mean? We're looking for, like, what?
地图  或者信件  书  或者
Like, a map, or a letter, or books, or...
卧槽  在这里找得找一年
Holy shit! It'll take a year to find something in here.
不知道上哪找那该死的万一
I don't know where to find this bloody staff.
看看这个小假马
Look at this little fake horse.
没准塞在它屁股里之类的
Probably stuffed in its butt or something.
男人就爱干蠢事
Guys do stupid stuff like that.
上面发生了什么
What is going on up there?
你查照片后面了吗
You checking behind pictures?
撕了吧  使劲撕
Just rip it. Rip it apart!
拿着  快点  我们快走
Just grab it. Hurry, let's make this quick.
真刺激
This is exciting.
- w我拿不出来  - 太好了
-I can't get it out. -Great.
我的天  攒了这么多东西
My God. Such a hoarder.
就好像里面进了人猿泰山一样闹
It's like having Tarzan in the house.
慢点
Slow down.
- 我看一眼  - 别去
-I'm gonna take a peek. -No!
拜托  拜托  接电话
Come on, come on. Answer me, come on!
该死  告诉我在哪
Damn you, tell me where it is!
想得美  先让我加入
Not so fast. I want in.
当维特维坎人  必须与众不同
To be a Witwiccan, you have to be a special person.
而你  并不具备资格
You, sir, are not.
让我进去我就告诉你  现在马上
Read me into the club and I'll tell you. Right here, now.
电话里吗  这太野蛮了
Over the phone? That is absolutely barbaric.
就在电话里  快点  英国佬
Over the phone. Do it, Englishman!
作为第12位弗尔根伯爵  以神圣的亚瑟王
As the 12th Earl of Folgan, by the power imbued
灌输的力量
by His Majesty King Arthur
以及他的圆桌骑士联盟为名
and his League of Knights of the Round Table,
我授予你  西莫·卢瑟福·西蒙斯
I now grant you, Seymour Rutherford Simmons...
- 进入  - 接受  不是进入
-Entrance into... -"Admittance," not "entrance"!
别唬我  说正确的词
Don't try to snooker me. Get it right.
够了  够了  快点告诉我
Enough, enough, enough. Just tell me! Now!
安静
Hush!
你自己安静点
Shut up! " yourselves.
n你们有什么毛病
What's the matter with you all?
七号书柜  C排
Stack six, row C.
快点  它们在溶解睾丸  快点
Hurry, man, they're dissolving scrotums. Let's go.
我在走了  别催  和你说话很困惑
I'm going! I'm going! It's very confusing talking to you.
快点  老人  k刈
Come on, old man, get there!
快点  西蒙斯  你说了今天不用工作的
Come on, Simmons, you said no work today.
我们一起去沙滩给你那双大白腿晒晒黑
Let's get your pale-ass legs and go to the beach.
我有正事  我保证只要五分钟
I'm working here, all right? Five minutes, I swear!
你总是说五分钟  也就是不的意思
You always say five minutes. That means no.
快去找罗德里戈和胡里奥开始准备
Just go get Rodrigo and Julio and get the game started.
我讨厌罗德里戈
I hate Rodrigo.
还有十分钟我就去找你
I'll set and bump with you in 10 minutes.
拜托  我还没忙完呢
Okay, come on, I'm in the middle of something.
我回来了
Okay, back.
在黑暗年代他们就知道末日会如何开始了
They knew way back in the Dark Ages where the end would begin.
赛博坦与地球共同存在
There is Cybertron and there is Earth.
只是他们从不叫地球地球
Only they don't call it Earth at all, they never did.
他们有别的名字
They called it something else.
总有一个会被另一个喜感
One will suck the other dry,
像巨大的魅魔一样  直到只剩一方
a giant succubus, until only one remains.
地球是宇宙之王
Earth is Unicron.
某天他会扬起角去对抗疯女昆塔莎
One day his horns will rise to fight the mad goddess Quintessa.
她会结束我们的星球让自己的星球复活
She will end our planet to resurrect her own.
我们走  快
Let's go. Hurry!
- 天啊  - 长老  快走
-My lord. -Cogman, go!
告诉我在哪
Tell me where it goes down.
我刚给了你
I just Dropped it to you.
角是找到法杖地点的关键
The horns are the key to the location.
为什么他们胡乱地散落在
Why are they spread out all over the Earth
地球  答案是  并没有
in a jumble? The answer, they aren't.
失控与大自然让他们分裂开来
Time and Mother Nature pulled them apart.
那是盘古大陆  超大陆
That's Pangaea. The supercontinent.
和圆桌的形状一样
It's the same shape on the Round Table.
弗尔根  看一眼
Take a gander, Folgers,
在那完美的圆形中心有什么
at what's smack in the center of that perfect circle.
聪明
Genius!
那是巨石阵
That's Stonehenge!
史上最伟大的谜团
One of the greatest mysteries of the ages.
直到现在都没人知道它的作用
No one understood its purpose until now.
- 除了我  没人  - 那就是开始的地方
-No one. Except me. -That's where it all begins.
你是大佬  快采取措施
You're the man behind the man. Do something.
交给我  西蒙斯兄弟  别担心
I'll handle it, Brother Simmons, fear not.
我从来没有兄弟
I never had a brother.
感觉真好
Feels nice.
去沙滩咯  准备好了吗
Beach time! Ready?
薇薇安跟着梅林
"Viviane followed Merlin."
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
我的秘密储藏间
My secret cupboard!
好了
Okay, okay.
薇薇安跟着美金
"Viviane followed Merlin."
只有梅林才能挥动魔法杖
Only Merlin could wield the magic staff.
梅林和小女孩  当然了
Merlin and little girls, of course.
海军博物馆  法杖肯定在哪
Navy Museum, that's got to be where the staff is.
天  原来一直都在我手中
My God, It was in my hands all along.
A队  快去  快快
Alpha team, go, go, go.
- 英国变形金刚反应部队  - 快走
-British TRF! -Come on!
我投降
I surrender.
主人  变形金刚应对小组正在紧追不舍
My lord, TRF is on our tail.
你怎么非把诱饵车停得那么远
Why'd you park the decoy car so far away?
你真是个蠢货
You are a fusspot!
好啦  别让咱俩被抓了  克格曼
Good. Don't let us get caught, Cogman.
我就擅长这个  大人
My speciality, my lord.
靠  你也不是非得杀人啊
Damn! You don't have to kill people.
闪开
Get out of the way!
这倒提醒我了  艾格尼丝打了个电话过来
Which reminds me, Agnes called.
她想知道你今晚有没有空跟她亲亲
Wondered if you're available for a bit of a snuggle this evening.
我倒想跟她亲亲  但你看我像有空的样子吗
I'd love a snuggle with Agnes. Do I look available?
闪开  混蛋  别挡路
Move, bitch! Get out of my way!
闪开  混蛋  别挡我的路
- 你好  是我  - 海军博物馆
- Hello. Yes. - Navy Museum.
皇家海军博物馆  我就知道
Royal Navy Museum. I knew it!
大黄蜂  我来吸引警察
Bee, I'm gonna divert the cops!
一个霸天虎已经被
A Decepticon has been seen...
你说霸天虎是什么意思
What do you mean, Decepticon?
- 刺激的来了  - 还搞刺激的啊
- Here's where it gets intense. - More intense?
大黄蜂
Bee?
该死的  他们把我们包围了
Goddamn, they're all around us
而我的路怒症又要犯了
and I just have so much road rage!
释放怒火吧  就这样
Actualize the rage. That's it!
想尝尝嘛
You want some?
克格曼  炸了他们
Cogman, blast them!
好样的
Good boy.
这是个死胡同
It's a one-way street!
车又不是我开的  是他开的
I'm not driving. He's driving.
不
No!
- 大黄蜂  往右边  有个跟屁虫  - 快走
- Bee, head right, haul ass! - Go!
只有这样你才能进大联盟
That's how you get to the big leagues.
真疼
That hurt.
什么鬼  你疯了吗
What the hell? You are out of your mind!
- 我们甩掉他们了吗  - 嘿  停下
- Did we lose them? - Hey, stop!
- 你没付钱  - 抱歉
- You didn't pay! - Sorry.
没事  有我呢  他们只不过特喜欢潜艇
It's all right, I've got them! They just love submarines.
他们可有点粗鲁
They're a bit rude.
没错  是啊  这就是新一代的年轻人
Yes, they are, aren't they? That's the modern generation.
而且这个博物馆要永久关门了
And this museum is closed for eternity.
小屁孩们  从潜艇上下来
All you boys and girls, off the sub now!
赶紧从潜艇上下来  闪开
Off the sub now! Move, move, move!
快走  死肥仔快走  快给我挤下去
Go on, push! Move your fat ass! Push! Squeeze!
走走走
Go, go, go!
这东西发动不起来
This thing isn't gonna run.
任务是在未经探索的深水之中
The mission's in deep, unexplored waters.
真是棒极了
It's wonderful!
还有弥漫着酸酸的男士麝香香水的味道
And the sour-sweet musk of men in close quarters.
其实有点恶心  真心的
It's quite disgusting, really.
但是这个
But now this,
史上最伟大的计划
the greatest mission of them all,
这是我一辈子所渴求的任务
one that I have longed for my entire life...
来帮助改变人类历史的潮流  知道么
To help turn the tide of human history, you know?
现在呢
Now, alas,
我在也不能加入你们了
I can no longer join you.
但是大人  您已经等这一刻等了71年了
But, my lord, you have been waiting for this moment for 71 years.
我知道  但我恐怕不是当骑士的料
I know, I know, but I'm not knighthood material, I'm afraid.
而且
And...
你们有你们的任务  我也有我的任务
You have your mission, and I have mine.
不不  你不可以把我们和那个
No, no. You are not leaving us in this tin can
四脚神经病一起丢在这个铁罐子里  这可不行
with that four-foot mental psychopath. I don't think so.
我更喜欢反社会分子这个称呼
I prefer the word "sociopath."
凯德先生  你一生所做的所有事
Mr. Cade, everything you've done in your life,
你的痛苦与折磨
your pain and your suffering,
丧妻之痛  又与女儿相隔
the loss of your wife, separation from your daughter,
再加经济情况窘迫
your financial difficulties,
这一路来风雨不断  只为了此刻
it's all just been a journey to this very moment.
你话真多
You talk a lot.
我觉得我也是
Yeah, I suppose I do.
亲爱的
My dear,
你爸爸把联盟交给你
your father left the Alliance to you,
并且只交给了你
for you alone.
她知道该怎么做
She knows the way to the staff.
祝你们好运
Good luck to both of you.
这又不是我今天干过的最奇怪的事
It won't be the strangest thing I've done today.
希望她还会开
Hope the old girl's still got it.
好运
Good luck!
那不是我干的
Okay. I didn't do that.
下潜了  你说下潜了是什么意思
Jumped? What do you mean, jumped?
二战老式潜艇刚刚自己下潜了
The old World War II sub jumped its moorings.
他们一个变形金刚里面
They're in a Transformer.
- 我能看看嘛  - 不行  我在看呢
- Can I get a look? -No, I'm looking.
你能让开么
Will you move?
伙计  别挡路  那是海水吗
God, get out of the way, man! Is that water?
- 大侦探真厉害  - 很明显是海水
- No shit, Sherlock. - Obviously, it's water.
你知道怎么开吗
Do you know how to operate it?
你知道怎么开的吧
You know how to operate it, right?
他说你负责开
He says you're in charge of this now.
- 快让我看看  - 别再碰我
- Let me see. Let me see. - Don't touch me again!
别吓唬我
Don't freak me out.
在外星飞船发生的事就留在外星飞船里吧
What happens in the alien ship stays in the alien ship.
我要干死你
I will eff you up!
海面  我海面视野良好
Surface, I have positive surface contact.
航道5205
Track number 5205.
潜艇一定在往大海开
The sub must be heading for open water,
直奔我们的突击小组
directly towards our strike group.
好的  我们必须阻止他们
Okay, we have to cut 'em off. Stop 'em.
用尽我们手头的一切资源
Use whatever assets we have.
联系祖鲁舱
Contact the Zulu module.
把我们所有的潜艇集中在那个阻塞点
Have all our subs converge on that chokepoint.
掌舵手  全体从侧面包抄
Helm, all ahead flank.
声呐有反应  外星信号
Conn, Sonar. Alien contact,
方位150  范围1000码
bearing 150, range 1,000 yards.
信号方向150
Contact bearing 150.
我们得把海豹突击队送到深潜船上  我们得追他们
We need to get SEAL teams in DSVs. We need to chase 'em.
控制台  这是一号  准备进港
Control. Ace One, going to the bay.
一号  准备进港
Ace One, going to the bay.
克格曼  那样正常吗
Cogman? Is that normal?
非常正常  女士
Perfectly normal, ma'am.
一个核潜艇正在我们船尾
A nuclear-class attack submarine is on our stern.
什么
What?
快点  跟紧我  快
Quick, follow me. Quick.
这是你的潜艇  不是我的
It's your sub, not mine.
我的潜艇  七个小时前  我还只是个大学教授
My sub? Seven hours ago, I was just a professor.
好了  解钩
All right, uncoupling.
好了  动起来  动起来  高速模式
All right, let's move. Let's move. Put it in high gear.
深潜船2号跟紧我们
DSV-2, stay on our tail.
声呐  外星信号  一千码  还在靠近
Conn, Sonar. Alien contact, 1,000 yards and closing.
潜艇上的警报可不是个好消息
An alarm on a sub is not a good thing.
他们为什么要我们到这里
Why did he send us up here?
他让我们冲在前面  我们就先死
He got us up front so we die first.
让他们知道我们在这里
Let's let them know we're here.
警告射击  一号炮管  一切就绪
Warning shot. Make tube one ready in all respects.
一号炮管发射
Shoot tube one.
声纳  外星物体  转为垂直方向
Conn, Sonar. Alien contact going vertical.
等下
Hold on!
声纳  对方掉头
Conn, Sonar. It's coming back around.
- 要撞击了 - 准备撞击
- It's gonna hit us!  - Brace for impact!
等下
Hold on!
声纳  对方要下潜了
Conn, Sonar. He's going deep!
我们现在暂时安全了
We're clear for now.
放手  你们俩有的是时间和地方
Hands off! There is a time and a place for everything.
但现在不行
This is not the time nor the place.
- 嘿  - 现在没空
- Hey!  - Not now!
- 你去哪  - 离开这里
- Where are you going?  - Away from here.
那个小变态自己把自己当成鱼雷发射出去了
That little sicko just shot himself out like a torpedo!
我知道  我又不瞎
I know! I saw it!
那些可是你的人
Those are your peoples.
下午好  那个  首相在吗
Good afternoon. Is the, Prime Minister in?
谁
Who?
首相啊  还能有谁  我有急事
The Prime Minister, who else? It's very urgent.
急事哈  你怎么不早说
It's urgent, is it? Why didn't you say so?
谢谢你  傻逼
Thank you. Dickhead.
我要从老门进  下午好
I'll use the old entrance. Good afternoon.
进去
Get in there.
抱歉
My... Sorry.
我胳膊上总有这东西
I just got this thing that was on my arm
而且好像还在乱动
and it's, like, just moving all around.
是啊  看起来  你要是
Yeah. It seems to not be, If you'd...
就是感觉有点滑滑的
It's just sort of slithery...
从胳膊滑到
Slipping from the arm to the...
- 是啊  往下滑了  - 往你的裤子里滑了
- Yeah, it's coming down. - It's going down your pants there.
小心点
Careful.
那东西紧吗  还是裹在里面
And is it tight or gripping on?
不疼  但我不知道他是干啥的
It doesn't hurt, but I don't know what it does.
就像个没用的外星垃圾
It's like some worthless alien junk.
我认为它是
I think the purpose... I think the...
我们会弄清它是干啥的
We'll find out what the purpose is.
如果你想的话
If... If you want to.
克格曼  这都是啥
Cogman! What is... What is all this?
世界末日
End of the world.
我觉得最后的晚餐还是很应景的
I thought a meal, a last meal, would be in order.
- 太棒了  我饿坏了  - 不许撒狗粮
- Great. I'm starving.  - No canoodling.
等会  克格曼
Wait, Cogman?
- 我女儿会  - 我奶奶说
- Yep. My daughter would... - So my grandma said...
我女儿一定会喜欢的
My daughter would love this.
我奶奶一定会
My grandma would absolutely...
她一直说我应该向前看
She keeps saying I've got to move on.
是的  我也想说  她会喜欢的的
Yeah, I was about to say. She would love it.
- 真的吗  - 是的  一直都是
- Really? - Yes, all the time!
- 他怎么说的  - 去约会去  找个男朋友
- What does she say?  - "Go on a date, get a boyfriend."
这算约会吗
Is this a date?
- 不  天啊  这不是约会  - 这只是
- No. God, it's not a date. No. - It's just that...
挺浪漫的
It's romantic.
克格曼寿司来了
Sushi a la Cogman!
看起来不错
Looks great.
有志者
No sacrifice,
事竟成
no victory.
总统在地堡里了吗
Is the President in his bunker?
是的
He is.
普京呢
How about Putin?
该死的
Son of a bitch.
你是新首相吗
Are you the new Prime Minister?
保安  立刻来我办公室
Security, my office, now!
抱歉  我用的老入口
I'm sorry. Well, I used the old entrance.
那个门是用来应急的
That door is used for extraordinary circumstances,
而现在的情形就很紧急
and these circumstances are quite extraordinary.
我长话短说
I will keep this very simple.
这个家伙
Nasty little fellow.
我要是让他出来  咱们都会死的很惨
I let him out, we all die terrible deaths.
你明白了吗
Do you understand?
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的名字是艾德蒙·伯顿爵士
Now, my name is Sir Edmond Burton,
女皇皇家海军  维基家族团
Her Majesty's Royal Navy, Order of the Witwiccans,
变形金刚在地球历史的守密者
keeper of the secret history of Transformers here on Earth...
- 维基家族团  - 维基家族团  没错
- Witwiccans? -Witwiccans, yes.
但它们都灭绝了
But erm, they all died out.
并不是灭绝了  目前还没有
Not all of them. Not yet, anyway.
但我需要你调动你所有的资源
But I do need you to marshal all your resources...
- 等会  你才  - 你最好闭嘴
- Hold on. You have just...  - Best shut up.
- 从墙里出来  现在就  - 听我说完
- Emerged from the wall and now... - Let me finish. Let me...
闭嘴
Shut up!
Shut up.
好了  就像我说的那样  我需要你调用
Okay. As I said, I need you to marshal
所有资源  所有军事资源
all your resources, all your military assets.
因为你也大概想到了
Because as you no doubt have surmised,
世界要毁灭了
the world is going to end,
而我知道何时何地会毁灭
and I know where. And when.
自从黑暗年代结束  你们是第一批看着这艘船
You are the first to see this ship since the Dark Ages.
你的护身符是解开这艘船的钥匙
Your talisman is the key to unlocking this ship.
声呐显示  还有大概800米
Sonar has about 800 meters.
我觉得四点钟方向有敌人
I think I got a bogey at four o'clock.
我渐渐能看清楚了
We're starting to see it through the murk.
下面有灯
There's lights down here.
天啊  快看  是艘大外星飞船
My God. Look at that. It's a big alien ship.
总部  你们看到了吗  真大啊
Topside, are you catching this? It's massive.
飞船知道我们来了
The ship knows we're here.
跟紧他们
Stay on his tail.
该死的
Shit.
门刚锁死了
The door just sealed.
试试那些管道
Try those tubes.
二号深潜船  跟紧了
DSV-2, stay close. Stay close.
总部  我们跟进了
Topside, we're going in.
无线电通信将会断开
We're gonna lose radio contact.
我们进洋流了
We're in a current!
稳住  稳住  稳住
Steady, steady, steady!
用机械臂保持
Use the arms to keep us...
- 你来控制  - 离墙远点
- Keep control! - Stay off the wall!
- 坚持住  - 离墙远点
- Hold it! - Stay off the wall!
现在怎么办
What now?
你是最后的骑士
You're the last knight.
你是厄尔的特殊人选  你自己想
You're the Earl's special guy. You figure it out.
走吧
Let's go.
我才不要下水
I'm not going in that water.
我的齿轮会卡在主轴上的
My gears would be sucked into my main shaft.
现在你俩都在我的黑名单上
Now you're both on my shit list.
我们遇到了盲点
We were blinded.
被太阳蒙蔽了
Blinded by the sun.
行星在群星的掩护下隐藏了自己的路线
The planet hid its approach behind our star.
看上去好像是故意的
It seems to be acting deliberately.
多次撞击正在形成
Dozens of strikes currently modeled.
阿尔法站将会承受第一次撞击
First impact will be Alpha Station.
没有救生舱
There is no escape pod.
两个小时后  地球也要遭殃
Earth will follow two hours later.
多米尼克估计会有千万人伤亡
Dominic modeled potential casualties in the tens of millions.
出现了两个月亮
There's two moons!
世界就要毁灭了吗
The world is ending?
有人说这将会是全球性灾难
Some are saying that it's going to be a global killer.
我们所知的人类文明
Human civilization as we know it
会在十二小时后改变
will change in 12 hours.
据专家说  破坏将是巨大的
The destruction, we're told by experts, will be immense.
简直难以置信
This is unbelievable.
是的  难以置信
Yeah, it is unbelievable.
老头想让我们干什么
What does the old man want us to do?
大黄蜂  绕开  找个别的路  快
Bee, go around, find another way! Come on!
什么  你在搞笑吗
What? Are you serious?
你觉得我想困在这种地方吗
Think I like winding up in a place like this?
它想让我们往这边走
It wants us to go this way.
交易员  那帮孙子确实带着我们的飞船回来了
Daytrader! Son of a bitch actually came through with our ship!
太棒了  我们要去英国
Excellent. We are going to England.
事情越来越复杂了  确实很乱
Things are likely to get nasty. Real nasty.
嘿  我能跟你们去吗  他也许需要我
Hey, can I come? He might need me.
我的小公主  当然  我不是你地球上的父母  快登船
Little lady, hell, I ain't no Earth parent. Hop aboard.
来一场去前线的旅行吧
Take a field trip to the front lines.
让我们喧闹起来
Let's go make some noise.
弄死他们
Let's give 'em hell.
我浑身充满干劲
I'm driving.
嘿  凯德  我虽然不太想承认这事  但是
Hey, Cade, I'm reluctant to say this to you, but
我觉得你真是  太勇敢了
I think that you're quite, you know, brave.
你是在夸我吗
Is that a compliment?
你也可以夸回我
You could throw one back my way.
好吧  待我组织一下语言
Well, that's got to happen organically.
我可是第一个进入潜艇的
I was the first off the sub.
停  停
Hold it! Hold.
我觉得就是在这了
I think it's here!
这是个坟墓
It's a tomb.
空间站  这里是休斯顿
Station, Houston.
安全区域配置程序第五页
Page five of the safe zone config procedure.
把推进器设置为自动
Take thrusters to auto.
他来了
It's happening.
现在就在我们的大气层
It's in our atmosphere now.
国际空间站就是第一个目标
ISS is our first hit.
推进器集合管都不好使了
Progress manifolds both failed.
没有推进器能用
No thrusters available.
马上就要接近你们了
Conjunction is imminent.
祝你们好运  一路平安
Good luck and Godspeed.
移动  移动  检查周围
Move in, move in, check up.
这是种仪式
Formality.
骑士总是在保护什么
Knights are always guarding something.
等一下  看这个
Hang on. Look at this.
这是凯尔特图案
It's Celtic.
这是梅林
It's Merlin.
传说是真的
It's real.
全都是真的
All of it!
等一下  这说什么
Wait, what does this say?
这句话意思是  没有人应该拥有它
It means, "No one shall have it."
等一下  我们费了这么大劲下来这里  看到所有这些
Wait a minute. We came all the way down here, all this,
你不打算打开吗
and you're not gonna open it?
我当然是要打开的
Of course I'm going to open it.
好  我们打开吧
Good. Let's go.
真的吗  来吧
Ready? Let's do this.
你一定是在逗我
You got to be kidding me.
我们费劲来到这就为了这个
We've come all this way for this?
为了看你曾曾曾祖父的破骨头
For your ugly great-great granddad's bones
被装在一个盒子里还有什么破棍
in a box and some stupid stick?
你一定是在逗我
You got to be kidding me.
我们就用这破棍怎么拯救世界
How are we gonna save the world with this?
我在家门前砍一截橡树就行了
I could've cut an oak tree down at my house and...
你能闭嘴么  行不
Don't say a word. Okay?
你那软香糯滑的小英音现在对我没用
The smooth little romantic accent's not gonna work right now.
- 我没说话  - 感谢上帝
-I'm speechless. -Thank God.
也许有人偷了权杖
Maybe someone stole it?
不  一定有别的什么东西  应该在这里的某处
No, there's something else. It's got to be here somewhere.
我绝不能空手而归
I didn't come all this way for nothing.
整个世界处于危险之中
The whole world's at stake.
同志们  仪器出问题了
Guys, the meters are freaking.
哪儿都能检测出热源  这些东西  它们
I got thermals everywhere. These things, they...
应该是还活着
They could still be alive.
你这个家伙什么情况
The hell happened to you?
是谁为梅林的权杖而来
Who has come for the staff?
攻击它  攻击它
Shoot him! Shoot him!
- 快走  - 快出去
-Move! -Get out!
我来给你做掩护  快离开这
I'm going to distract him. Get out of here.
- 我有这个权杖  - 快打它
-I have the staff! -Hit it!
保护权杖
Protect the staff.
把它的眼睛干掉
Take his eyes out!
脚下这东西正在动
Wo, this thing's moving.
围住她
Corner her!
嘿
Hey.
把武器放下
Drop the weapon.
放下
Do it!
你放下枪  否则我扔下去
You drop it, or I will.
你不知道你在干什么  伦诺克  停下
You don't know what you're doing, Lennox. Stop!
我想要的就是这个武器
All I want is that weapon!
- 来啊  打我啊  - 不要
-Go ahead, shoot me! -No!
只有我能操纵它
Only I can wield it.
来啊
Go on!
开枪啊
Do it!
打我啊
Shoot me!
你不知道你现在在做什么  伦诺克
You don't know what you're doing, Lennox.
别出手
Don't.
保护权杖
Protect the staff.
我也是来找这把权杖的
I've come for that staff.
擎天柱  你干啥呢
Optimus... What are you doing?
把权杖给我
Give it to me.
是我  我是凯德  我们并肩战斗过的
It's me, Cade. We fought together.
我为我自己种族战斗  我自己的星球
I fight for my own kind! My own planet!
- 凯德  - 这不是你  擎天柱
-Cade? -This isn't you, Prime.
把权杖给我  人类
Give me the staff, human.
凯德
Cade?
我要杀了你
I will kill you.
把权杖给他
Give it to him.
现在
Now.
我看谁还敢挑战我
Who dares to challenge me?
一切都不对劲  大黄蜂
It's all wrong, Bee.
发生了一些事  那不是擎天柱
Something happened. That is not Optimus.
你得找到他  大黄蜂  记得ZB-7模式吧
You got to find him, Bee. Remember ZB-7?
你得变回那种模式
You got to be that Autobot again.
听着  你得回到潜艇里  行么  离开这
Look, you got to get back to the sub, all right? Get out of here.
等一下  那你呢
Wait, what about you?
大黄蜂能保护我  该我上场了  快走
Bee's always had my back. It's my turn to have his. Go.
好了  快回到潜艇里
All right, get back to the DSV.
让上面的人知道我们弄丢了权杖
Let them know up top that we lost control of the weapon.
收到
Roger that, sir.
你听到他说的了  快回到潜艇里
You heard him. Back to the sub!
我们要找到他
We're gonna find him.
快走  我们要往高处走
Come on, we got to get to the top!
我擦  我勒个大擦
Holy shit. Holy shit.
我们能做到  快来
We can make it! Come on!
小心  巨浪来了
Watch out, big wave coming!
我是复仇至尊
I am Nemesis Prime.
尔等区区蝼蚁
You are nothing!
快走
Move it!
飞机会落在14到16区
Air's gonna be on station 14 to 16.
技术中心  这看起来像一个外星飞船的表面
TOC, it looks like we have a surfaced alien ship.
雷电4号看到了擎天柱
Lightning 4 has visual on Optimus.
擎天柱  擎天柱  停
Prime! Prime, stop!
擎天柱  请你停下来  别这么做
Prime, you got to stop! Please! Don't do this!
看着我  擎天柱
Look at me, Prime.
你在干什么  那是大黄蜂啊
What are you doing? It's Bee!
擎天柱  你不能这么做
Prime! You can't do this.
擎天柱
Prime!
停  别这么做
Stop! No!
我是大黄蜂  你认识最久的朋友
I am Bumblebee, your oldest friend.
擎天柱
Optimus,
我愿意为你献出生命
I would lay down my life for you.
大黄蜂  你的声音
Bumblebee. Your voice.
自从赛博坦星球毁灭了
I have not heard it
我就再没听过你的声音了
since Cybertron fell.
我做了什么
What have I done?
你错失了杀死宇宙大帝的机会
You blew your chance to kill Unicron.
我就知道你做不成
I knew you couldn't do it.
你结束了  擎天柱
Your time is over, Prime.
你失败了
You failed.
你背叛了赛博坦
You turned your back on Cybertron.
现在你就看着地球毁灭吧
Now you will watch Earth die.
不
No!
情况不怎么好
Not going so well.
凯德
Cade!
你背叛了你的种族
You betrayed your own kind.
没有  擎天柱  起来
No, Prime, get up!
汝选择了错误的队伍
You chose the wrong side.
守卫骑士要杀了我
The Guardian Knights are going to kill me.
昆塔沙是最大的骗子
Quintessa is the great deceiver!
对你的审判就是死亡
The judgment is death.
没有牺牲就没有胜利
Seglass ni Tonday.
凯德  我辜负了你
Cade, I have failed you.
我毁了地球
I have doomed Earth.
地球  宇宙中唯一一个地方
Earth, the only place in the universe
可以让我称之为
whose people let me call it
家
home.
只有你才能弥补过失  擎天柱
Only you can make it right, Prime.
没有你我不能成功
I can't do it without you.
我们只有一次机会
One moment, that's all we got.
取决于你  擎天柱
It's up to you, Prime.
因为没有你
Because without you,
我们都会死
we all die.
机不可失
It's now or never.
我的兄弟们
My brothers,
我永远不会再背叛你们
I will never betray you again.
我是擎天柱
I am Optimus Prime.
要拯救地球  我们得去赛博坦星球
To save Earth, we must go to Cybertron
杀死昆塔莎
and destroy Quintessa.
飞船来了
The ship is coming.
景色真美
It is beautiful.
擎天柱给了我们最后阶段的坐标
Optimus Prime gave us the coordinates for the endgame.
是一个点火室
It's an ignition chamber.
武器就在那里
The weapon's going up there.
让掠夺者和卫星启动
Get Preds and satellites eyes on.
找到那个地方  准备好参战
Find it and prepare to engage.
独眼兽  21000英尺
Cyclops, 21,000 feet.
定位目标  点火室  我们找到了
Eyeball target, ignition chamber. We found it.
擎天柱的坐标很准确
Prime's coordinates are good.
连接点火室  目标在视野中
Contact, ignition chamber. Target in sight.
点火室  点火室
Ignition chamber, ignition chamber.
我们得搞明白是怎么个原理的
We've got to figure out what makes it tick.
我们得关了它
We've got to shut it down!
快来  快来  快来
Come on, come on, come on!
看到你很高兴
Good to see you.
我们离开这里  我们走
Let's get out of here! Let's go!
将军  我们准备要高空跳伞到
General, we're gonna prep a HALO jump
那个点火室
on that ignition chamber.
在那些藤蔓中飞机定位不准
Planes will never nav through those vines.
伦诺克  相信我  我们的船就在那
Lennox, trust me. That's our ride right there.
我们汽车人的飞船  把鱼鹰直升机落在那
Our Autobot ship. Put the Ospreys in that.
飞船会在那接我们
It'll get us up there.
汽车人的飞船会载着鱼鹰直升机
Autobot ship's gonna drop the Ospreys.
滑翔至登陆区  风险很大
They'll virtually glide to the LZ. It's gonna be high-risk.
他们在20000英尺要干什么
They want to do what at 20,000 feet?
先生  有个小姑娘  一位女士  事实上是一名老师
Sir, there's this girl. Woman, actually. Teacher.
- 牛津大学的  - 还会打一点马球
-Oxford. -She plays a little polo.
真是太有意思了
Well, that's fantastic.
他们会帮她进到点火室
They're gonna break her into the chamber
把权杖偷出来
to steal the staff.
好吧  这可能是你出的最馊的主意了
Okay, that is the dumbest idea you could possibly have!
个人来说  我依靠物理和数学
Personally, I'm gonna rely on physics and mathematics
来拯救星球
to save the planet,
而不是什么神秘主义  童话故事  还有什么妖魔鬼怪
not mysticism, fairies, and some hobgoblins.
我一生就是为了这件事
I've lived for this.
我生来就是要毁灭星球
I've lived to kill a planet!
为了我们的星球  我激活这个入口
For our world, I activate this portal!
开火
Fire!
尔等可怜的人类
You wretched human!
你收到了我的信息  你把所有人都带来了
You got my message. You brought everyone here.
跟我来
Come on.
嘿
Hey!
我找到了擎天柱
I just found Optimus Prime!
他会解决这堆烂事
He's gonna deal with all this shit!
他会救我们的
He's gonna save our asses!
我带了一队人马  兄弟  我带人来了
I brought the troops, man. I brought the troops.
骑士们  汽车人们
Knights, Autobots,
结局绝对不会是这样
this cannot and will not be the end.
为了拯救地球和她的人类
To save Earth and her people,
我们要偷昆塔莎的权杖
we are going to steal Quintessa's staff.
只有你  薇薇安  能拿回来
Only you, Viviane, can take it back.
我会带路到她的房间
I will lead the way into her chamber.
当光辉岁月铭刻在星云之上
And when the account of the ages is etched into the cosmos,
后人将会知道
let those who exist long after us know
这是我们最荣耀的时刻
that this was our finest hour.
我太爱这个人了  每次都鸡皮疙瘩掉满地
Love that guy. Goosebumps every time.
我还没跟他说你好
I never got to say hi.
他们来了
Here they come.
你觉着这些人够吗
You think there's enough?
不  远远不够
No, not even close.
我的主人  福尔根主人
My lord! Lord Folgan!
我做到了  克格曼
I had it, Cogman.
我完成了我的使命
I had my moment.
是的  我的主人
You did, my lord.
这是我工作中最艰难的部分
This is the hardest part of my job.
看着福尔根家族的人死去
Watching Folgans die.
谢谢你  克格曼
Thank you, Cogman.
继续辅佐家族吧
Carry on.
我服务过的所有的伯爵中
Of all the earls I have had the pleasure to serve,
到现在为止你是最酷的
you were by far the coolest.
我探测到权杖的能量了
I have found your staff of power.
只有一个人能伤害到我们
There is only one who can hurt us.
我感受到了她  她不能进来这里
I felt her. She must not enter.
我的军队会阻止他们
My army will stop them.
看着我们的星球恢复  他们的星球毁灭
Watch as our world heals and theirs dies.
一个新世界诞生了
A world reborn!
要来了
It's coming.
这些碎片会砸死我们
It's gonna crush us.
现在赶紧上飞船离开挤压区
Get that ship clear of the crush zone now!
- 我们得离开这里  - 快到鱼鹰直升机上
-We got to bail! -Move to the Ospreys!
快走  快走  快走  快到直升机上
Move, move, move! To the Ospreys!
那东西就在我们上面移动
That thing's gonna roll right over us!
快走
Move!
最初的部分要开始移动了
Preliminary numbers are starting to come in.
抹去城市  数百万人会死
Literally scraping away cities. Millions will die.
它在用地球的地热能源
It's using Earth's geothermal energy
来重构和重建它自己  对吧
to reconstitute, to rebuild itself, all right?
如果我们的地核冷却了  就像现在这样
If our core cools, which is rapidly cooling right now,
地球的磁场就会消失
the magnetic field dissolves, exposing us
我们将暴露在大剂量的宇宙辐射里
to high levels of cosmic radiation.
也许你们会理解这个
Maybe you'll understand this.
地球会变成一台微波炉
The Earth becomes a microwave.
我们就是爆米花  爆米花胀袋
We're the popcorn. Jiffy Pop bag goes
砰
boom.
我们就烧焦了
We fry.
面相看着不善呀
Very mean looking.
那些家伙不过是胆小鬼罢了
They look like wusses to me.
对  他们不堪一击
No, they all messed up.
还有两分钟  两分钟
Two minutes! Hey, two minutes!
- 这个能干掉霸天虎吗  - 不能
- That thing kill Decepticons? - No.
我们能
We do.
真的有一群勇士愿意牺牲一切
"A few brave warriors willing to sacrifice all."
我还告诉我的学生那些都是胡扯的
I told my students that was bullshit.
出发了  走吧
Load out, let's go!
你明天打算干嘛
What are you doing tomorrow?
你现在就问我这个吗
Are you asking me that now?
对  是
Yeah, I am.
没计划吗  很好
No plans? Good.
快上飞机吧
Get in the plane.
- 我们出发  走吧  - 都动作快点
- Let's go, let's go! - Let's step it up!
系好了  这一趟会很颠簸的
Strap in. It's gonna be a rough ride.
- 系紧点儿  - 我会帮你扣好的
- Tighter. - I'm gonna hook you up.
下拉到底  对吧  就这个吗
Pull it down tight, right? Just this one?
你跳出去
You jump...
- 然后拉这个  对吗  - 这个是我该拉的  对吧
- Then pull this, right? -This is the one I pull, right?
拉这个  光拉就行  玩命拉就行了
Pull? Just pull it? You just pull it as hard as you can?
你没事儿吧
Are you all right?
能借你的手机用用吗  我给女儿发条短信
Can I borrow your cell phone? I've got to text my daughter.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
All right.
谢谢你
Thank you.
已看到目标
Target in sight.
接近  点火室
Contact, ignition chamber.
攻击小队  行动  行动
Strike package. Execute. Execute.
开战  开战  开战
Fight's on, fight's on, fight's on.
不明物接近  不明物接近
Bogeys inbound. Bogeys inbound.
大黄蜂  上飞船吧  祝你好运
Bee, get to your ship. Good luck.
三十秒后跳伞
Thirty seconds to drop!
但愿着陆的时候能容易点儿
Those birds better be softening our target.
你这让我怎么能放心呀  伦诺克
You're not giving me that warm, fuzzy feeling, Lennox.
鱼鹰飞行限高一万两千英尺
The Osprey's flight ceiling is 12,000 feet.
我们已经翻倍了
We're double that.
空气太稀薄  螺旋桨吃不住力
The air's too thin, the rotor's got no grab.
我们得硬着陆了
We're gonna be coming in hard.
- 全是坏消息  - 没错
- It's all bad news. - Yeah.
没事儿吧  耶格尔
All good, Yeager?
有什么要说的吗
You got something to say?
你和你的人一直都在抓我
You and your guys never stopped hunting me.
是命令  你当时和他们是一伙的
Orders. You were with them.
什么他们
With "them"?
我信仰的可是一个伟人
I believed in one of the great ones.
他是擎天柱  还有他的队伍  我一直都很相信他们
Optimus Prime. And his crew. I never lost faith.
你们不信他  全世界都不信他
You didn't. The whole world didn't.
现在你们又想和我一起了
Now you want to fly with me.
好吧  我很感谢你们安排此行  谢谢
Well, I appreciate you guys making the trip. Thank you.
拿下那个权杖
Get that staff,
我们就可以回家过年了
we all go home.
伦诺克  你的队伍待命
Lennox, your team is to hold.
战斗机在各个方向都损失惨重
Strike fighters are getting shot down.
不  必须要趁现在  飞行员  现在跳  走
No, it's now or never. Pilots, go now! Go!
等等
Hang on!
哇哈哈
Chihuahua.
- 你在这里干什么  - 我不知道
- What are you doing here? - I don't know.
但是你说过我们是家人
But you said we were family.
不  我不是要你  现在就得把她弄下去
No, I didn't mean... We got to get her off here now.
现在说不合适了吧
It was probably a bad idea.
六架飞机出动了
Six birds out of the nest.
所有鱼鹰就位
All Ospreys clear.
向目标推进  向目标推进
Push the target, push the target.
都抓紧了
Hang on!
- 哇哈哈  - 会没事的  会没事的
- Chihuahua. -It's okay. It's okay.
所有战机  分散队形  分散队形
All fast movers, distract, distract.
让敌人远离这些鱼鹰
Keep those enemies away from the Ospreys!
正前方  敌机
Bogeys dead ahead!
控制台  分散队形  分散队形
Control, spread it out, spread it out.
那些战斗机最好分散掉敌方兵力
Those fighters better distract those enemy ships!
前方敌机来袭  一点钟方向
I got bogeys coming in hot, one o'clock.
三架敌机  小心
I got three bogeys.
注意旋翼
Watch the rotor!
长官  三号机不行了
Sir, bird three just went down!
那里就是降落区域
There's our landing zone.
端掉那个火力点
Take that big gun out.
蝰蛇号  注意那个火力点
Viper Flight, focus on that gun.
抓紧了  我们要触地了
Hold on, we're going down!
要硬着陆了
It's gonna be a hard hit.
别飞出边缘
Don't slide off the edge!
小心  小心  小心
Brace, brace, brace!
二号没了  二号没了
Two's down, two's down.
做好撞击准备
Brace for impact!
- 快下飞机  - 带着这个伙计
- Out of the bird! - Grab a buddy!
快下飞机  快
Get out of the bird! Go!
我们有后援吗
Do we have a Back up?
敌方战斗机
Enemy fighters!
那个火力点实在太猛了
That gun emplacement is tearing us apart!
点火装置在那儿  就在前面
There's the ignition chamber, dead ahead!
空中掩护过不来  来不了
Air cover not coming. Unable.
走起  大黄蜂
Let's ride, Bee!
灭了他们
Let's kick ass!
向右边弹坑前进  我们走
Push right to the crater! Let's go!
和探长一起干他们
Pinned down with the Hound!
没辙了  擎天柱在哪儿呢
No way. Where's Optimus?
他们说他来不了了
They said he never made it.
我们遇到一个很猛的火力点
We got the big gun on us!
我们被压制了
We're pinned down!
无法接近目标  无法向前推进
Negative to target. Unable to advance.
快回来  伊莎  - 伊莎
- Get back here, Izzy! - Izzy!
我很快就回来
I'll be right back!
这么个烂摊子真是太让人不爽了
It's just a cluster effin' thingamabob!
小灵通
Sqweeks!
听着  我需要你过去把那个火力点炸了
Look, I need you to blow that gun up!
不去
Mommy.
你个儿又小  长得又丑  没人会看到你过去的
You're small and you're ugly. No one's gonna see you coming.
快炸了它
Blow it up!
求雨鬼
Infernocus,
变形吧  干掉他们
transform. Kill them!
我的弹药不够对付那个家伙
I don't have enough ammo for that thing.
我来搞定他
I got him!
大黄蜂和热破不行了  汽车人不行了
Bee and Hot Rod are down! Autobots down!
擎天柱在哪儿
Where's Prime?
哎  我滴妈
Ay, chihuahua.
打不过去呀  将军  火力压制太猛了
It's a no-go, General. We're pinned down!
好吧  之前的办法都不起作用  对吧
Yeah, well, that hobgoblin stuff didn't work, did it?
我还有一招  物理手段怎么样
I got a Hail Mary. How about physics?
好吧  我刚刚做了模拟
Okay, I just did the simulation.
它就像是泰格·伍兹用九号球杆铲起了
It's like if Tiger Woods was making a big divot
一大块草皮
with his nine-iron.
史杜  别挡着  拜托
Stu, out! Come on, man.
好了  这儿有好一大块都是被那些藤条给拉住的
All right, there's a chunk right here that's held up by thin vines.
你必须炸断藤条  使用战术核武器炸断藤条
You gotta blow up those vines, use tactical nukes to blow out
好让它摆动起来
the vines and let it swing.
然后地心引力起作用
Okay, you let gravity do the rest.
装置接着就停了
The chamber comes down,
能量传输停止了  地球就能保住了
the energy transfer stops, and the Earth is saved.
不用谢
You're welcome.
给我接战术核武部门
I need tac-nuke authority.
伦诺克  带着你的人撤离  任务结束了
Lennox team, we are pulling you out. Mission's over.
给即将抵达的战机指明目标
Laze targets for incoming strike fighters.
然后听我的撤退指令
Then I'm ordering you to bail.
收到  有图像了
Roger that. Picture's up.
我看见了  我看见了
I see it, I see it.
我们有新目标了  往上三点钟方向
We got a new target! Three o'clock high!
激光标记新目标给过来的飞机看
Laze the new target for incoming birds.
他们要把整个玩意儿都移平了
They're gonna bring that whole thing down on us.
听着  我们不能放弃擎天柱  好吗
Hey! We're not giving up on Prime, okay?
他会来的
He's gonna be here!
他们刚刚改了整个计划  我们进不去
They just changed the whole plan. We can't get inside.
- 什么  - 我们的行动结束了
- What? - The operation is over.
我们再呆着  就死定了
We stay, we're dead.
我必须进那儿去
I have to get in there!
所有人拿好降落伞  我们要撤了
Everybody, grab your chutes, we're bailing!
你
You.
打  打  打
Fight, fight, fight.
开打
Fight's on.
干得漂亮  小朋友
Good job, little friend.
- 激光瞄准目标  - 快  快  快啊
- Laze the target! - Move, move, move!
我们走
Let's move!
快撤  我们掩护  快
Let's move out! We got you covered! Move!
擎天柱
Optimus.
好
Yeah!
你个丑八怪
You ugly mess!
你是不是忘了  我是谁
Did you forget who I am?
我是擎天柱
I am Optimus Prime.
汽车人  出击
Autobots, attack!
激光瞄准
Laze the target!
瞄它  瞄它  瞄它
Laze it, laze it, laze it.
确认激光标记  确认目标上的激光印记
Laser paint confirmed. Laser paint confirmed on target.
来吧
Come on!
银箭导弹  发射
Silver arrows, fire.
导弹已发射  导弹已发射
Missiles away, missiles away.
走  走
Go, go!
走
Go!
- 来吧  我们走  - 我觉得这臣妾做不到啊
- Come on, let's go - I don't think I can do this.
还有九秒钟
Nine seconds.
要回家了  伊莎
We're going home, Izzy.
小姐  别扔下我
Mademoiselle, don't go!
薇薇安在哪儿
Where is Viviane?
她走了  老大  他们全都开溜了
She's gone, boss. They're all chickening out.
要是你错了呢  伦诺克  要是不管用呢
What if you're wrong, Lennox? What if it doesn't work?
会管用的
It's gonna work!
听着  我们一起跳  好吗
Look, we're doing this together, okay?
- 我们走  - 拜托了  击中  击中吧
- Here we go. - Hit it, hit it, hit it...
我们得走了  我们在撤退了
We got to go! We're bailing.
- 你在做什么  - 为了那些脏兮兮的旧书
- What are you doing? - It's just dusty old books.
什么
What?
等等
Wait!
她这是开我玩笑呢  坏了
She's got to be kidding me. Shit!
薇薇安  进这里来
Viviane! Get in here!
好的  我的好姑娘
Yes! My little lady.
等等
Wait!
凯德
Cade!
指挥部  请注意  点火装置正在坍塌
Command, be advised, ignition chamber is tumbling.
重复  点火装置已经支离破碎  即将倒塌
I repeat, chamber is broke loose. It is falling.
能量传送还在进行中
The energy transfer is still continuing
倒计时  还有55分钟就会撞击
T-minus 55 minutes and counting.
这竟然没有起作用
I can't believe it didn't work.
将军  我在降落过程中
General, I'm in my chute.
还能看到能量在传送
The chamber is still arcing power.
看来没用
I don't think it worked.
- 不  - 抓住
- No! - Hold on!
跟我来  由我来带路吧
Follow me. I'm gonna lead the way
好了  就在那了
Okay, there it is.
抓住权杖呀  薇薇安
Grab the staff, Viviane!
好了  去吧
All right, go!
小心  小心
Watch out, watch out!
把时间停止
Stop the time!
我要爆了你的头  威震天
Gonna blow your head off, Megatron!
再见  笨蛋
Sayonara, bubblehead!
威震天  杀掉她
Megatron, kill her!
我们曾经是兄弟
We were brothers once.
曾经而已
Once.
我们要失重了  失重了
We're going weightless. Weightless!
- 抓住我的手  - 好的
- Grab my hand. - Yes!
别让它跑了
Don't let it go!
昆塔莎  滚出我们的星球去
Quintessa, get off our planet!
你个叛徒
You traitor!
跟我的朋友打个招呼吧
Say hello to my friend,
大黄蜂
Bumblebee.
致命如蜂
Sting like a bee.
我来救你
I'll save you!
我来停住时间
I stop the time.
这算明天了吧
Is it tomorrow yet?
每一段传奇的最深处
At the heart of every legend,
都蕴含着真理
there is truth.
一群勇敢的灵魂团结起来
A few brave souls unite
拯救他们的世界
to save their worlds.
我们能成为自己生命里的英雄
We can be heroes in our own lives,
每个人都行
every one of us,
只要我们有勇气去尝试
if we only have the courage to try.
你救了擎天柱
You saved Prime.
我们的命运总是彼此交缠
Our fates were always intertwined.
但这一刻  我们的世界合二为一
But now our worlds are joined as one.
我们要重建我们的星球
We need to repair our planets.
如果我们要生存
Work together...
我们就必须齐心协力
If we wish to survive.
疯狂的一家
Crazy family?
你干的不错  哥们  真心不错
You did good, bro. Real good.
地球的深处还藏着一个危险的秘密
A dangerous secret is buried deep inside the Earth.
这个星球不止表面的那些苟且
There is more to this planet than meets the eye.
我是擎天柱
I am Optimus Prime,
呼叫所有的汽车人
calling all Autobots.
是时候
It is time
归乡
to come home.
你迷路了吗
Are you lost?
我是不会那么做的
I wouldn't do that.
不要碰他
Don't touch him.
他不喜欢那样的
He doesn't like it.
谁不喜欢什么
Who doesn't like what?
宇宙大帝
Unicron.
但是我可以向你展示怎么杀了他
But I could show you how to kill him.
哈瓦那  古巴
英格兰  英国
氮气宙斯
骇客
莫霍克
华盛顿特区
约旦
中国北部
纳米比亚  西非
牛津大学
弗尔根堡  英格兰 英国
赛博坦星球
英格兰  中世纪
敌人
禁止非法闯入
违者将被击毙
车辆和人员需接受检查
芝加哥
喷气推进实验室
加州理工学院
变形金刚反应部队全球指挥中心
1600年后
Seglass ni Tonday：It means No sacrifice, No victory
没有牺牲就没有胜利
TOC：Technical Operation Center，技术操作中心
Nemesis Prime:复仇至尊  也叫大黑天
伦敦  英国
侦察系统
数据控制器
深宇宙系统
你好  亲爱的   我叫惹泼
Bonjour cheri, Je m'appelle hot rod
惹泼
ut rud
不要妄想胜利
它在看着你
为胜利而战
快来参军
乔托·迪·邦多纳  意大利画家与建筑师
史蒂芬.霍金
德·拉瓦锡 现代化学之父
古斯塔夫·马勒 奥地利作曲家、指挥家
维特维坎家族团 1901
山姆·维特维基 变形金刚 1 2 3部男主
弗雷德里克·道格拉斯 废奴运动代表人之一
艾德蒙·希拉里  新西兰登山家和探险家，
在和夏尔巴人向导丹增·诺盖的合作之下
他和丹增·诺盖成了可证明的记录中
最早成功攀登珠穆朗玛峰峰顶的人
我不认识你
I don't know you
唐宁街十号  伦敦
美国第五舰队  英国
变形金刚5：最后的骑士